<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name = "anomaly_desc">
        <item>"Warning: You have been hit by the baldy-bald psychological attack. If a non-bald person reads this, they’ll be granted the privilege to go bald at an extremely rapid pace. If one wants to stop this from happening, they must be assigned to work on this Abnormality. In addition, if you find 10 or more strands of hair on your pillow in the morning, it is recommended to peruse this encyclopedia article at least three times."
            "Bill: I had an amazing dream today!
            Brian: What, did you win the lottery or something?
            Bill: When I got to work, everyone here was bald! Everyone including you! Maybe even people outside of this corporation!
            Brian: Umm… I think you’ve been pretty stressed lately. Why don’t you go take counseling?
            Employee Bill suffered an unfortunate accident with Singing Machine that day. Right after the incident, Abnormality Bald-is-awesome! appeared in the facility. We all cherish the memories of Bald Bill."
            "If one comes in contact with the Abnormality, they will talk or write about the positive aspects of baldness for about an hour, and ultimately make themselves go bald.
            If you become bald, you can save time because you don’t have to wash and dry your hair anymore, allowing you to be richer than others.
            No adverse reactions will happen if a bald employee is assigned to work with the Abnormality.
            The bald don’t have to worry about hair loss.
            If a non-bald employee is assigned, they will shave off their own hair.
            Bald people can even reflect light off their head and blind their opponents like a solar flare!
            This Abnormality’s goal is to make every single human on Earth bald.
            We won’t need light bulbs in our facility if there are more bald employees, because light reflects off their heads. This will allow us to save a tremendous amount of our budget.
            If a non-bald employee is sent to work with the Abnormality, it’ll produce less energy.
            Did you know that every single noble in Europe during the Middle Ages was bald? They’d change their wig everyday!"
            "We’ve just added some new rules to the company code of conduct:
            + If you ever spot a XXX mocking their coworker with alopecia areata, they will be labeled as a hirsute, and will be banned from using the lounge for an indefinite period.
            They will also be forbidden from joining the company’s debate club “Questioners of the absence of bald Barbies”, the gourmet meetup “Octopi over Squid”, and the environmental protection group “Save the Bald Eagles”. (These regulations will be lifted as soon as the rulebreaker’s hair strand count goes below 1.)
            Lastly, I dedicate this article to employee T.H. who is quietly taking balding medicine next to me right now."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality in the shape of a training dummy used to train up-and-coming managers."
            "Rumor has it this Abnormality was chosen to be used for training as it is the most docile and tame of any that we have extracted. It’s called a training dummy “rabbit”, but it doesn’t seem to enjoy carrots. It likes people.
            If it escapes, it is merely following the employee as they leave its Containment Unit."</item>
        <item>"It takes the form of a girl burnt to ashes. Even though there's nothing left to burn, the fire still doesn't extinguish."
            "A matchstick impales the girl's body like a stake. Usually, the match is always lit, while the Abnormality shows no sign of activity. Because of this, employees often speculate that the matchstick may be the Abnormality's true body. However, recently, the ashen figure was seen crying, according to witnesses."
            ’s Research Log>
            "The charred body represents the child's crumbled hope, while the ever blazing flame represents the obsession for affection. It's always in conflict with the contradiction between these two.” “We paid a boatload and that's all they have to say?"

            "Well, she’s like a ticking time bomb. No one can tell if she’s in a good mood or not. We just hope that we won’t be the one blown up before entering the Containment Unit. She won’t get any better, we can only try and keep her from getting worse."
            "I never thought the abnormality would be able to escape. Maybe we were getting careless, but it seemed that all it could do was burn up the match stuck in its body. Yes, our response was a bit late. (Omitted) Most Abnormalities that try to escape would attack the employees in front of them, but this one didn't show any aggression toward the nearby employees. Instead, it headed to a different department, the most crowded place in the company. If we didn't suppress it at the door, half of the people here wouldn't be in one piece."</item>
        <item>
            A silent Abnormality that understands the conflict between good and evil. Its empty eye sockets stare at all those who encounter it.
            A giant skull that is attached to a cross, it wears a crown of thorns. It floats about 2 meters above the ground."
            "While its appearance is bizarre, it is rare to record an incident of violence against employees involving this Abnormality."
            "It feeds on the “evil” that seeps out during conversations between people. The assigned employee must kneel before it (standing appears to be acceptable) and present their “evil” by confessing their sins to it. The way it feeds is unknown."

            "We have cataloged the sins a person can commit into three levels.
            Level 1: A small lie or action that either goes unnoticed or can be shared in jest.
            Level 2: Sins that are more serious and only shared with the closest of friends.
            Level 3: Sins so profound that they cannot be shared with anyone. These will be taken to the grave.
            Employee had been assigned to confess a Level 1 sin. Energy production via the Abnormality increased by 12%.
            Employee was assigned to confess a Level 2 sin. Energy production via the Abnormality increased by 15%.
            We assigned employee to confess a Level 3 sin. 1 minute and 48 seconds after the employee was sent in, a bright flash of light was seen. The light was so bright that it could be seen outside of the Containment Unit. Immediately following the light, there was a facility-wide power outage. The phenomena lasted for 2 hours. Employee lost 6 years of their memory.
            Further experiments were canceled. Scientific ethics decree that all footage of those who participated in the experiment is to be kept sealed. However, the incident left us no choice but to review the footage of the Containment Unit."
            "Employee : "This happened during at around 4:00 PM. Anyways, there was a railway about 20 minutes from my house. Some of my good friends and I decided to dress as forest animals. One of us chose to go as a deer. It was a crude costume, it could hardly be called one to be honest. Just a pair of clumsily made antlers and a dark outfit with some deer-like spots on it. (Omitted)
            I don't know how our ‘deer’ friend wandered into the woods. We didn't even notice he was missing for maybe an hour. We searched for him and finally found him in some bushes. We called out his name, and I'm not sure if it was from relief of finally finding us or what but he started sprinting towards us.
            And that's when we heard it; the gunshots. Bang! Bang! Bang! When I came to my senses, I saw his blood splattered all the way to my feet. After that, not one of us dressed up as an animal ever again. That’s all. By the way, is this really supposed to work?" "
            Observation Log #4_435
            "Its eye sockets are empty. It is a skull after all. But I doubt it’s blind. It certainly has its gaze fixed on me, and I can somehow feel that it’s listening to me. Confessing to it does lighten my heart, admittedly."
            "Afterwards, we investigated the incident in the employee’s hometown to get a better picture. We learned that a boy named Justin was shot and killed in a deer costume by hunters during hunting season. Unlike the employee’s confession, Justin was repeatedly bullied by other kids. Witnesses said they heard the kids shout “Run, Justin, run!" right before the gunshot. After the incident, the kids at the scene moved out of town, and deer hunting was banned in the area."
            "Honestly, you can’t expect all of our employees to give honest confessions to that skull. Around every one in ten employees will tend to say something that is not completely true. It’s a bit different from a lie. You can say that it’s a subconscious excuse they make.
            They distort perspectives to justify their actions, even though they are aware that they should be telling the truth. Once this happens, the confession is no longer truly a confession. Yes, I’m talking about you trying to justify your tardiness for 5 minutes now!
        </item>
        <item>"A humanoid Abnormality that looks like it would go and fight villains for peace and justice at any moment.
            It is friendly toward every employee and is able to engage in casual conversation. It believes that it is a hero born to save the world, and takes considerable pride in it.
            When it shows signs of anxiety or doubt while conversing with an employee, its appearance and personality will undergo an adverse change within 4 days, and it will display symptoms of dissociative disorders.
            The definition of good and evil are fixed in its mind. Some assume that when the Abnormality’s beliefs lead to a horrible doubt about the existence of evil, it will choose to become evil to negate that doubt.
            All parameters will return to normal after the negative phase passes, and the Abnormality will have no memory of the behavior it exhibited during that phase.
            Audio Log_1 Employee: How are you feeling today?
            Magical Girl: Good. The world is at peace, and it’s quiet around here. Peace is a great thing to have. It means there aren't any villains around, right?
            Audio Log_2 Employee: You're looking a bit down today.
            Magical Girl: Still fine. The world is peaceful, and it's... (The Abnormality fell silent and did not wish to continue speaking)
            (Omitted)
            Audio Log_3
            Employee: ...Are you alright?
            Magical Girl: Why is it still so peaceful? You see, the whole purpose of my life is to defeat villains. It's as if the world is trying to say it doesn't need me. Really, why is it still so peaceful? Oh, did I mention that I'm a magical girl? To keep the world's peace, I was born. But today, it's quiet today. (The Abnormality continued to murmur incomprehensible words to itself)
            Audio Log_4 (The Abnormality endlessly mumbles to itself, without even noticing the employee in its containment)
            Magical Girl: The world can be divided into good and evil. I am on the side of justice. If I am on the side of good, then someone has to be on the side of evil. Without someone to play the villain, I can't exist. Then, who is going to protect the world? Audio Cuts Out
            Audio Log_5: Level 3 or above access required
            This is part of an audio record obtained during the rampage on the date of *****. The Abnormality used a radio installed in the facility to call the Emergency Planning Team. - (Continuous Sobbing) Employee: This is the Emergency Planning Team. Please identify yourself. - I think, I... I did this. I, I couldn't stop myself. It's my fault. I ruined everything. I betrayed the people who were kind to me. I don't remember why I did this. Employee: Could you elaborate on what happened? - I don't know. They aren't moving. There's so much blood. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
            (Omitted) Three bodies were found in the Abnormality's Containment Unit. The Abnormality lost all memory of the incident afterward."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality that resembles a large, raggedy teddy bear. It's missing some fur and only has one eye.
            The old ribbon around its neck hints that it may have received much affection from its previous owner. There is a name on the ribbon, but it is too tattered to be discernible. It seems that it knows it has been abandoned, and looks dejected.

            I was on the night patrol. I didn't feel the need to pay attention to Happy Teddy since it was harmless for the most part. I just looked inside the Containment Unit to check on it. Teddy was hugging someone tightly. I thought it was *****, the employee who was in charge of Teddy for a while, working late. But something was odd. I entered the unit and called *****'s name, but they didn't answer. I immediately pressed the emergency button to call in reinforcement. Turns out, ***** had been in a coma for 8 hours. They were in Teddy's arms the whole time. 
            An Old Letter, Stamped with Rejected
            Remember what was written in the employee manual? Do NOT have personal feelings towards Abnormalities. At first, I didn't get what that was supposed to mean. Does it even make sense to develop any emotion toward those monsters in the first place? It's okay. They are monsters. Between the two of us, we can call them that. 'Happy Teddy Bear' was the second Abnormality you took charge of. I guess you must’ve thought that not all Abnormalities are monstrous after seeing it. The figure of an old, abandoned teddy bear may have brought up old memories of yours. Teddy seemed to like your hugs. Yeah, it would actually produce more energy when you were around. And in no time, they put you in charge of Teddy. You probably felt some kind of responsibility for it, right? I started getting worried as you visited Teddy's unit more and more often. It felt as if you were visiting an orphanage for volunteer work.
            ... It seems Teddy saw you as its new owner. Maybe you'd have been happy to hear that. But, you see, Teddy never wanted to be separate from its owner ever again
            You probably always promised that you'd return. But it couldn't understand. I heard that you miraculously survived. And that they spent an hour trying to separate you from Teddy's embrace. Though others may forget about you. I will always remember you. May there be a miracle."</item>
        <item>"A pair of elegant red women's shoes. The design is antique, but there is no telling where and how they were made.*
            It overwhelms the mind with the urge to try them on. The changes that occur from wearing the Abnormality are first visible in the eyes of the wearer.
            The next observable change is that the wearer is unwilling to take off the shoes. They will also act upon any and all desires that they may have subconsciously suppressed. If someone attempts to hamper them from acting on their desires or tries to take off the shoes, the shoes will control its host, which sometimes leads to murder.
            It is unknown whether the host’s will is involved in the process, but taking into consideration the sharp increase of one’s desires and aggressiveness, the host’s primal urges seem to remain intact.
            Employee F1230:
            *****was a nice person. Well, they were also kinda a celebrity. They always told us that our job was something to be proud of. They knew how to deal with all kinds of Abnormalities. But it was our biggest mistake to let them enter that Containment Unit. We never thought a pair of shoes of all things would do any sort of harm. At some point, ***** was wearing the shoes, grinning from ear to ear. It was uh, well it was quite strange. That wasn't a smile. It was... (Omitted).
            Blood was all over the place. The tapping of the shoes echoed in the corridor. I closed my eyes and played dead. I saw one of my colleague’s head rolling around on the floor. The shoes stopped right in front of me and stood still for such a long time. Eventually, they moved past me, and that was right when I passed out. (Omitted)
            I heard they couldn't take off the shoes and had to cut their legs. No one ever saw ***** again after that, but those who’ve been here long enough will recall the incident.
            Footage from Corridor Camera Z3_493:
            *****: So the work on your part is all done right? I just finished mine. That little match girl is still in the same state. It's so frustrating. Wanna grab some coffee at the lounge?
            *****: You know, *****, there's something I've been thinking about for a long time.
            *****: Let's talk when we get to the lounge. I'm just too tired right now. Hey, are you wearing shoes? Only staff footwear is allowed during work.
            *****: That's not important, *****. What's important is that we're alone at the moment.
            *****: What are you talking about... Wait, what exactly are you wearing on your feet? Y-You didn't wear it, did you?
            *****: *****, I've loved you for a while.
            *****: Take it off, now. Do you even realize what you're doing right now?
            *****: I was thinking about why you wouldn't love me back. It's Emily, isn't it? You were so busy looking at Emily that you didn't even notice me, right?
            *****: I... I-Is that an axe you're holding? And you're bleeding from your ankles.
            *****, I'm begging you, please take that off.
            *****: So all I need to do is get rid of Emily! Wait here for a bit, it won't take long. You have to stay still till I come back.
            *****: Please snap out of it. Please...
            *****: If you wanted to stop me, you should have done that the day we first met.
            ***** stunned ***** with their weapon and went to the lounge. Fortunately, no one else besides ***** was harmed, including Emily. ***** was soon removed from the company database. They were entirely aware of what they were doing. They admitted that the shoes only encouraged them to do what they always desired. A response team handled the suppression of *****.
            Afterward, the Red Shoes ran away, tearing *****’s ankles off their body. It took a total of 23 minutes for them to be suppressed, contained, and returned to their Containment Unit. ***** died from excessive blood loss. ***** only sustained minor injuries, but elected to resign due to excessive psychological trauma.

            We received the report that employee ***** was allured by the shoes and was roaming the corridor. We immediately ordered employee F3054 to suppress her.
            She was a veteran employee with vast experience in suppression, so we expected her to suppress a female employee without any trouble. But she didn’t return, and when others found her, employee F4002 was unconscious with both her ankles severed, while employee F3054 was maniacally trying to remove the shoes from the severed feet."</item>
        <item>"A music box with an impressive sculpture of a dancing ballerina.
            When wound up, a sad melody begins to play. No one knows when it was made or who made it, but it doesn’t seem to be new judging from the slight skips in the song.
            There are a few phrases crudely carved on its surface: “Do you remember this melody? The professor used to play this song when the students were sleepy. Happy birthday.” 
            Listening to this music box will make anyone feel like everything will be okay in the end, lifting their fatigue. However, excessive listening will make one lose grip on reality, and be driven mad."
        </item>
        <item>"An Abnormality taking the form of an old and feeble woman. Anytime someone enters its Containment Unit, it will talk to that person.
        What it tells differs from time to time, however, it will always commence with “Dearie, dearie, would you like to hear a story?”. This story could be a lullaby, an unspecified poem, a nursery rhyme, a common children’s story, or something entirely new.
        It knows every children’s story and will not stop recounting until the listener finally leaves

        She may be the loneliest of all the Abnormalities. She’s filled with loneliness, and tells her tales to fill that void. Well, every story needs a listener. When someone enters her room, she’ll try to fill that void. Of course, listening to her is a very dangerous thing. She knows every story on Earth and even those that cannot possibly exist. Our minds can’t cope with such a thing. She could fry your brain in an instant."</item>
        <item>"It takes the form of an unborn fetus. Its skin is covered in a mucous, sticky liquid.
        The Abnormality’s bulged eyes are usually closed and small veins can be seen on its body here and there. It always seems unsatisfied, but what exactly it needs is undetermined. It has a great obsession with being “fed” - and if it is not “fed” regularly - its stress levels rise drastically. Once it reaches a certain level of stress, it cries out loudly in way that mentally harms all who may be around it.


        Employee F2706: I’ve never seen it smile. It always seems to want something, but we can never fulfill its desire. I guess the reason why its cries are destructive is ‘cause its unsatisfied needs are so strong. When I was a newbie here, none of my colleagues would tell me what exactly we fed it.
        I thought it was just some weird milk or something like what other normal babies would eat up. It is a baby after all underneath all that grossness. But that wasn’t the case. It only eats human flesh. Can you believe it? To stop it from crying, we have to hold a drawing every so often. Do you know what that means?


        When I first heard that the ‘Nameless Fetus’ had to be fed, I thought we’d have to give it food with like, a spoon or something. It looked too weak to do anything, and its mouth isn’t fully developed either. Later when I found out that it ate meat, I thought it’d have to be chewed up by someone first so it would be soft enough to eat. When I asked my working buddy about it, he laughed and said: “No way, that’s ridiculous. We just need to leave the food in the unit and go.”
        I still thought about how in the world that fetus could eat stuff. I wondered if we served it some kinda succulent steak that’s not even available to us in the cafeteria. Out of curiosity, I decided to sneak a peek at the feeding process of the ‘Nameless Fetus’. Only level 3 and up employees are assigned to that process, but I was able to attend cause I made up an excuse that I was covering for someone.
        As I nervously watched, wondering if my lie would be worth it, some people came along with large plastic bags. Does it eat that much? And when they opened the bags, I could only gape in horror. They were human corpses. And the baby ate it. How? I don't even want to imagine it. It had a large scar on its stomach; I really thought it was some kind of scar. Like a large flower, its stomach would open, dripping with slimy liquid. It was the greediest creature in the world. That day onward, I was a vegetarian.


        I'm Pauly. I've worked for Lobotomy for about a month now. My parents are really proud of me for getting into a Wing like this, and all my friends are jealous of me. I still make a lot of mistakes, but someday, I'll be as capable as my coworkers.
        There's a special employees-only event held by our company. No one knows when or why this event is held. Even my coworker who’s been here for 5 years doesn’t seem to know. When the event starts, a giant roulette begins to spin. Everyone stops what they're doing to stare at the roulette and see who'll be the lucky winner, with desperate looks on their faces. The name of every single employee is written on that roulette. Whoever ends up being selected, they're extremely lucky. They'll be promoted and transferred to another branch of the company, Headquarters.
        In addition, their family will be gifted with an unimaginable fortune. At the headquarters, you don’t have to worry about being attacked by Abnormalities, or need to bid farewell to your dead colleagues. My senior, *****, really hopes that they’ll get picked eventually. You see, their father got into an accident one day, and it takes a lot of money to keep him alive and well. I really hope the roulette picks ***** someday.

        When my senior's name showed up on the roulette, I congratulated them with all my heart. Though, they didn’t seem too happy for some reason. Others gave them a hug, one by one. Everyone was crying for some reason. They said goodbye to me, shedding tears while trying to force a smile. I haven't seen them since. I’m sure they’re working under much better conditions with a really nice salary!
        But, when I try to bring them up in conversation, people stop talking as if I've spoken some sort of taboo. I still remember the last thing they said to me before they left. “One day you'll understand. The meaning of the desperation on their faces when the roulette spins.”

        The manager holds the specific right to call a special event for all the employees in the facility without any cause for occasion. When the event starts, a giant roulette will spin and select one lucky employee’s name. That employee will be promoted, transferred to a different branch, and their family will receive a yearly pension. No personnel are allowed to invade the manager’s right to hold this event. The following information is forbidden to the public eye:

        Conditions required to hold the event:
        - Data Access Restricted
        - Data Access Restricted
        - The crying of ‘Nameless Fetus’ has reached its peak.

        The roulette will select an employee that satisfies one of the conditions below
        1. Questions the true purpose of the company.
        2. Conducts or plans unauthorized^ experiments with the Abnormalities.
        3. Maintains an excessive curiosity about the Abnormalities, and conducts or plans unauthorized^ observation on them.
        4. Is incapable of working due to physical or psychological trauma.
        ^ “Unauthorized” signifies that it is “Unauthorized by the corporation or Angela”.

        The following actions will be taken with the employee selected by the roulette
        1. Expunging all records the company has about the employee.
        2. Sacrificing the employee to the Abnormality.
        3. Informing the employee’s family that they have been transferred to another branch."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality in the shape of a woman against the wall. Over time, her unbearable sorrow grew into a mournful obsession, covered in countless, lengthy hairs.
        As she is always facing the wall, not a single person has seen her face. While she occasionally talks to herself and weeps quietly, it is impossible to have a meaningful conversation with her. Despite her human appearance, it is impossible to discern what she is really looking at or her true intentions.
        She will attempt to talk to or pique the interest of those who are about to leave her Containment Unit. However, one should never look back in response, as it may cause mental damage. Certain rumors insist that one may turn to stone upon looking back, but this is clearly not true.

        There is only one important rule to follow: Ignore her. She always tries to draw our attention. She mutters incoherently in an attempt to have those in the room pay closer attention to what she’s saying. She’ll even plead or whisper maliciously when someone is about to leave in the hopes that they may instinctively look back. The subconscious is a threat to your own health in her presence; it is important to have your guard up and to be aware of what is occurring when you are in the room with her. If you forget the warnings for even a second and let your guard down, you may find yourself looking back towards here. I have another warning to leave to all who read this: Do not let this insidious Abnormality learn your name. If she learns your name, she may use it to trick you into turning around. No matter what you hear or what she may do to tempt you while you are in the room with her, DO NOT and I repeat DO NOT under any circumstance look at her. Curiosity is a luxury you must NEVER indulge in when you are in her Containment Unit.

        Employee F5004: ***** was a colleague of mine for whom I cared deeply. Well, I cared for all my coworkers, but ***** was different. The amount of passion they poured into their work was something I have rarely witnessed in life. Anyways, I have no idea how she, that Abnormality, learned *****’s name. Maybe someone called it out to them while they were inside the Containment Unit and she heard it. We should have sent two in for work with her. The common procedure was to have a team of two sent into the Containment Unit, but as you know, we’re always shorthanded. Besides, that Abnormality was low on the threat scale. If we followed the procedure and sent two inside, the powers that be would not have been happy about it one bit. (Omitted)
        Well, you know the rest. The day the incident happened, ***** was sent to the Containment Unit as usual, but they didn’t come out for a long time. I know ***** was a prompt and diligent worker, so I headed straight for the Containment Unit fearing the worst. Thankfully, I found them without even a scratch, but the kid looked out of it. Like, way out of it. (Omitted)
        The next day, the kid was resigned. I heard they sent ‘em to an asylum, but no one ever saw ***** again. The kid just kept staring at the wall, murmuring and not responding to anyone. That was the very last time I saw *****. No one knows what happened inside the Containment Unit. You won’t find it out from the kid either."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality whose appearance resembles a human, but cannot and should not be human. It periodically devours employees and wears their shell. The skeleton and organs are misplaced during the process, so it takes a bizarre form.

        The Abnormality does have a tongue, however, it has no knowledge of speech and as such cannot talk; it can only make meaningless sounds. There is no telling what is inside its shell, but its skin continuously wears down, so there is a need to change and maintain the outer layer. It is insensible to pain; it may break its own bones or cut itself up to escape through a small crevice.

        Bit by bit, we discovered that this Abnormality may be evolving. It demonstrates behaviour similar to the character of the person who used to be its shell. It even makes attempts to equate itself with human beings.

        When it escapes, it wears the skin of the person it killed and mimics them. Then, without any sign or forewarning, it reveals its true/second form. In its true/second form, its resemblance is much similar to that of humanity in comparison to its earlier form. The new form is confirmed to possess bipedalism, properly aligned organs, and the addition of greater physical strength. All the employees are afraid of this form.

        A Warning of Something
        If it has been confirmed that it has escaped and stood on two feet, there is only one thing you can do. Straighten up your posture, gather your hands neatly, and pray to whatever you believe in and observe the situation as it unfolds.


        “Just like how we observe Abnormalities as employees, ‘Nothing There’ observes us. Then it puts on the shell of an employee and thinks of itself as the employee that just died. The sight of that thing eating one of us is horrifying beyond words, just trying to think about it might drive me mad. Heading to its containment to check the state of its shell is a toil on your mind, too. Imagine that a colleague of yours who you chatted with just a few days ago is now sitting in that room, neck snapped, guts exposed, walking on all fours, drooling like a beast. (Omitted)

        That’s not all. When I was still a new employee, no one else was willing to enter its Containment Unit, so I was forced to go work with it. It looked even worse than it does now. It was in the shape of a horribly deformed human. What’s worse, it tried to mimic humans. Doing stuff like looking into a mirror, mumbling to itself, or trying to fix its skeletal structure; it’s as if it was trying to mimic ‘us’. Who knows, it might get good enough to casually walk among us one day.”

        Warning:  Only employees Level 3 and higher are permitted to read this document.
        (This recording is of a call from the Containment Unit’s emergency phone. Phone systems are installed in every room of Abnormalities of Risk Level HE or higher to enable quick threat response.)

        Employee 1: Please pick up, please pick up. This is the Containment Unit of ‘Nothing There.’
        The Emergency Response Department (ERD): Hello, this is the Emergency Response Team. What’s the problem?
        Employee 1: I need a stun gun right now! There’s an emergency happening right now!
        ERD: Can you please specify the reason?
        Employee 1: The Abnormality… (the sounds of something breaking can be heard) It’s ripping up the employee.
        ERD: Excuse me?
        Employee 1: It’s killing my colleague!
        ERD: We’ll respond immediately. Please identify the employee being attacked.
        Employee 1: It’s uh… wait one sec. Their name’s *****. Control Team. I’m, *****. Also Control Team.
        ERD: Confirmed. What’s currently happening to your colleague at this exact moment? Employee 1: Yeah, just please hurry. We need a weapon to control the Abnormality. (A loud noise can be heard, presumably the scream of the colleague) Oh god, this is…
        ERD: What’s happening?
        Employee 1: The Abnormality is attacking my colleague. It’s literally ripping them apart, I can’t do anything. I repeat, we need a weapon to control the Abnormality.
        ERD: The Emergency Response Team has been dispatched. They’ll arrive shortly.(Omitted)
        ERD: *****? What’s happening now? Is it still attacking your colleague?
        Employee 1: Yeah, oh no. I think it’s done now.
        ERD: Has it stopped attacking?
        Employee 1: No, I mean. My colleague’s… He’s dead. Yeah, he’s dead alright.
        ERD: How can you be so sure?
        Employee 1: Well it’s because he looks… he’s…
        ERD: Has he been ripped up somehow? What body parts are damaged?
        Employee 1: All of them.


        Just like how we observe Abnormalities as employees, ‘Nothing There’ observes us. Then it puts on the shell of an employee and thinks of itself as the employee that just died. It mimics the employee's usual behaviour, the way they talk, likes and dislikes, and every other visible trait. We can only guess how carefully, and for how long it has been observing the employees to imitate them. What I’m trying to say is, we can’t just treat it like some ‘dumb scary monster’. Even now, it could be strolling about wearing the shell of someone we know. This Abnormality is becoming more and more like a human. Its transformation is getting faster too. I get goosebumps just thinking about it. If the time comes when we fail to recognize it, that will be the day the company falls. We must stay ever vigilant when dealing with this Abnormality.

        The following is a recording of the abnormal behavior an employee exhibited in their last moments after they became a shell of ‘Nothing There’.

        Employee 1: Manager, manager!
        Employee 2: Man, you've been looking for the manager for quite a while now. You've been acting really weird today y'know? With that weird smile and all.
        Employee 1: ...
        Employee 2: Anyhow, I sure hope we get pasta in the cafeteria for dinner today. I’d love some of that with thick bacon.
        Employee 1: ...
        Employee 2: Oh, we just got an emergency notice. It says the last employee to work with Nothing There should get to the counselor's office immediately.
        Employee 1: ...
        Employee 2: Wait... Wasn't that... You?
        Employee 1: ...
        Employee 2: Hey, say somethi—
        Employee 1: Manager, manager! Manager!

        The second employee proceeded to take immediate action upon hearing that. However, ‘Nothing There’ tore out of the shell of the first employee, revealing its beginning form. The recording only includes audio files, so what exactly happened or what kind of behavior the employee exhibited still remains a mystery. The shell with ‘Nothing There’ inside tries its best to mimic the behavior of the employee it tried to kill moments ago. The actions of the last employee it eyed, their final words, those sort of things. And the many shells cried out one word, “Manager”."</item>
        <item>"This Abnormality is a phenomenon with no visible form. It was discovered when employees began to exhibit shared symptoms when entering a specific area of the facility. They all suffered hallucinations of a specific nature, and their mental corruption increased.

        After setting a radio’s frequency to 1.76 MHz, we waited. Following 12 minutes, a mysterious voice was heard through static. It was difficult to make out what it was saying, but it appeared to be in distress and was asking for help.

        17 minutes in, the voice stopped and 3 loud explosions were heard, which were then followed by 2 smaller explosions. It can be assumed that the situation the voice was in was chaotic, as based on the various levels of screaming that could be heard.

        23 minutes in, all was silent.

        Once 25 minutes passed, the radio began to emit smoke. We thought the machine had fried, but no fault could be found.

        Continuing past 30 minutes, everyone in the area was suddenly filled with rage and started to exhibit the desire to assault one another with extreme aggression.

        Following the incident, all employees who took part refused to seek counseling (we couldn’t make it mandatory as no one was injured). It is still unknown what caused the collective rage.

        Afterwards, unknown noises and hallucinations started to occur near the Containment Unit. This is a recording of the day we must never forget. It brings us to a chaotic place—forgotten by many—that must never be forgotten."</item>
        <item>"It takes the form of a long cuboid machine.
        At first glance, all it seems to be is a simple industrial grinder. However, the existence of it having an individual “will” meets the criteria to be classified as an Abnormality.
        When approached or touched, the employee will become delirious and throw themself into the Abnormality's mechanical body. Afterward, the machine's ventilation fan will quickly shut off, and the sound of the Abnormality operating can be heard from within. This process takes about 5 minutes.
        After a few experiments, we have concluded that the Abnormality desires to gain music from this interaction.
        There is no detailed research into this Abnormality’s “music”, however, there is a hypothesis that it has a special characteristic that attracts humans in correlation to their specific behaviors or psychological counseling records. If one of our employees has been determined to be addicted to the music, they will need to be treated quickly to prevent any collateral damage.

        I just wanted to write the observation report and get out, but he was acting odd.
        I warned him not to get too close, but ***** took one step closer. He said he'll let me hear a fantasy, then he opened up the lid and jumped into the machine. The lid closed and a loud noise came from inside the creature. There was no way to know what was happening, but I was too terrified to do anything. (Omitted)
        In the dark, I realized that thing was playing an instrument. Crushing and cutting *****'s body, it was creating a rhythm. As I was contemplating my horrific realization, the lid opened again. Bits and pieces of ***** were in there. So little that you had to wonder what happened to the rest. (Omitted)
        NOTICE, MUST READ: Symptoms of addiction to the music of ‘Singing Machine’>
        1. Attempts to bring other employees to the Containment Unit of ‘Singing Machine’ by physical force.
        2. Dilated pupils.
        3. Greatly reduced concentration and cognitive abilities.
        4. Refusal to listen to other forms of music.
        Please list any additional symptoms that are found and immediately report any employees that are suspected of the noted symptoms.

        Date: XX/XX/XXXX
        Employee M1840 went missing in the company. 2 days later, on the XXth, part of a corpse was found inside the ‘Singing Machine’. Genomic analysis revealed that the corpse belonged to the missing employee. The employee was a new hire who had only worked for the company for 3 months, and they had no record of an assignment to work with the Abnormality.
        The culprit was found to be employee *****, who was in charge of the ‘Singing Machine’. ***** confessed after extensive investigation. “I know it's crazy, but I had to hear that music again. It was stuck in my head for months. I performed all kinds of experiments.
        When the machine takes in a cat, it plays for 1 minute, a large dog, 2 minutes and 30 seconds. But nothing could compare to the music it makes when it eats a human.
        ...It might sound ridiculous, but I feel satisfied, having heard it once more."</item>
        <item>"An abnormality that loves art and tries to get the entire company to listen to its music.

        The conductor not only corrects musical errors, but is also responsible for creating the best ensemble and taking command of the music. A conductor's skill can be determined within 5 minutes at the podium. The moment the conductor opens the score, the performers read the conductor's eyes, actions, and aura to see if the person is worthy to lead them. Without the understanding and harmony between them, the macroscopic significance contained in the score cannot be expressed. Therefore, an outstanding degree of influence, leadership, and eloquence are essential qualities for a conductor to have...(Omitted)

        1st Movement: Calm and Slow(Adagio)
        The conductor begins to direct the apocalypse.

        Movements 2: Cheerful and Fast(Sostenuto)
        Employees start to forget everything and show fervent adoration toward the symphony. The emotion soon turns into internal insanity, driving them to attack anyone near them.

        Movements 3: Accelerando

        The orchestra gives impetus to the music, bringing the entire department to its demise.

        Movements 4: Stringendo

        When all the performers have gathered, the music that no one can hear but everyone can listen to begins.

        Finale: Con Fuoco, Ma Non Troppo
        The music shall perforate your entire being.

        "</item>
        <item>"A mechanical Abnormality whose humanoid body is composed entirely of galvanized steel. It holds a giant axe with both hands, but does not show any activity, as if it's unable to move.
        The friends were imperfect in one way or another, so they helped each other to fill what they were lacking and embarked on a journey to make their wishes come true. The Scarecrow wanted a brain, the Tin Woodsman wanted a heart, the Cowardly Lion wanted courage, and Dorothy wanted to return home. The one they thought to be the great wizard instead gave the Woodsman a lead heart.
        But you're a machine, that means you were built to serve humans. Don't you understand? Machines don't need a heart. Good job making it all the way here though, take this as compensation. Be sure to tell everyone waiting for you that your wish definitely came true.
        Some left with satisfaction. The friends departed and were never to be seen again. The hard, cold lead was depressing.
        The Tin Woodsman couldn't agree with this. In anger, he swung his axe through the wizard's heart. The warm heart was pulsing vigorously. He shoved the lead into the wizard's now empty chest. For the first time in his life, the Woodsman started laughing at the sight and felt a pleasure he'd never had before. Grabbing a chunk of mushy hearts, he shoves it into his chest. There will never be enough hearts.
        Once a Woodsman, he now fells people instead of trees. This is a forest full of hearts. No matter how many he cuts down, the forest still remains dense. A kind person would carry a warmer heart..
        When the heart is lost, the Woodsman will fall to his knees in sorrow, clutching his empty chest. As if begging for the only thing he has left not to be taken."</item>
        <item>"A queen lives alone in the frosty winter forest.
        Like how every story starts, Kai was a child with a kind heart. When the shards of a mirror made by an evil fairy were scattered on everyone's heart, Kai began to see things he didn't want to see, or need to see.
        He left the small village he grew up in. In an unforgiving blizzard, Kai met the Snow Queen. He became curious of the world beyond his knowledge. He felt as though everything he knew amounted to so little.
        The Snow Palace he reached was so cold, but the Snow Queen's kiss froze his heart, and he couldn't feel the cold anymore. There was no joy in the palace, only the long winter night. Gerda was strong enough to remain unpierced by the mirror, and brave enough to go on a journey to rescue Kai. So she set off towards the Snow Palace.
        The journey was agonizing. Gerda was hurt and pained, sometimes she cried. However, eventually, Gerda met Kai. Spring arrived with blossoming roses. Its warmth melted the Snow Queen's palace, and the piece of mirror in Kai's heart evaporated without a trace. Then, left all alone, the Snow Queen... (Omitted)
        I remember the day we put her in the cryo-coffin with our own hands. At some point, her joyous laughter was gone. She just cycled through laughing and crying, and eventually she was found in a bathtub soaked in red with her wrists cut.
        We did not believe in death. I will have her reconstructed from the machines I have detested for my entire life, but have become the only answer. She would have been disgusted by me for this, dying in that bathtub. However, we were too far down the road filled with remorse and regret to feel any sort of guilt.
        ……
        One day, it spoke to me.
        'I remember you. You were a kindhearted person.'
        The moment I heard it, I was seized by the urge to destroy what I had created with my own hands."</item>
        <item>"A large, many-eyed bird that patrols the dark forest with an everlasting lamp. Unlike regular birds, it lacks wings and has long arms instead with which it can pick things up.

        ...(Omitted) would stare intently at anyone it found, young or old, and bite their head off. There is a tale of a beast that lies in the deepest, darkest part of the forest who dazzles creatures away never to be seen again. To protect all creatures from the beast, the big bird burned all of its feathers to make a wick, and then made a lamp that would burn forever. With this eternally lit lamp, the big bird wandered the forest, warning the creatures to not stray too deep into the trees. Thanks to the large bird, fewer creatures fell victim to the beast in the forest. However, it was still concerned for the creatures still being killed by the beast. An idea struck the big bird’s mind: “If I kill the creatures first, then no one would be killed by the beast!”
        Since then, only rumors of a beast that would bite your head off flew around the dark forest. It is said that the beast carefully examines and stares at its victims to see if they are the beast that lures helpless creatures away. This is a tale from a town in the Location Redacted area. We heard the tale from the town's oldest inhabitant, *****. Although there is a general assumption that the tale was told to prevent children from entering the forest, it is uncertain who first inherited the tale.

        “We can’t do anything while the Abnormality has its eyes open. It stares intently, and as it keeps staring…(Omitted). This is why we need to put it to sleep first. We can only begin working when all of its numerous dozens of eyes have entered into slumber.”

        And it turns out that the tale was not made up. We could find this large bird in the forest. Right after that, we tried to look for the ‘Beast that dazzles people.’ We searched through every nook and cranny of the forest. Investigated every single creature in detail. A month later, we came to this conclusion: There was no such ‘beast’ in the forest. Except for that big bird.”

        “This Abnormality is completely ignorant of the common perception of death. The Abnormalities that reside in this corporation can be placed into two different categories. The first category is those who understand perfectly well what the concept and meaning of death is, and will attack our staff with the intent to kill. The second has those who are aware of the concept of death, but attack without malicious intent. This Abnormality we have contained here fits into neither of these two categories. To this bird, death in itself is salvation. If it just ripped off the head of a poor little girl who got lost in the forest, to it, there was no mistake, malice, or murder. It thinks it’s just saved the girl from the beast.”

        "</item>
        <item>"A white cleaning robot with distinct red eyes that look like a pair of buttons. It always keeps its surroundings neat and tidy.
        It was originally a mass-produced helper robot intended for domestic use.
        The writing on its back says: An innovative invention that can clean, cook, and even serve as light security using various tools attached to its limbs. Built to perform efficiently and quickly! Manufactured by XX Inc.
        It recognizes a bad mood as a sign that the surroundings are dirty, and promptly enters cleaning mode. It will alert its status by stating lines such as Contamination detected - Commencing cleaning.
        However, the limbs are equipped with sharp instruments instead of cleaning supplies. Rumor has it they were supposed to be used for cutting meat, but they were made to respond to the clean command by accident. There is no way to confirm whether this is true.
        It has determined that the screaming humans make after it cleans is a sign of a job well done, and a prompt to continue its cleaning.
        An Audio Record found within the Robot
        ???: Oh~ It's the new helper robot.
        ???: Let me see! I wanna see!
        ???: You wanna touch it ████? Then try turning it on and play with it.
        (A phone rings)
        ??? : I'll be right back after I get the phone, okay?
        (Sounds of buttons being pressed)
        Helper Robot: Hello! I am your friendly Helper Robot. How may I serve you?
        ??? : Cleaning! I want to help mommy cleaning!
        Helper Robot: Environment contamination 70%, filth level mild. Commencing cleaning mode.
        ??? : Wow! It's cleaning! It's clean...
        Helper Robot: Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
        After a few seconds of shrieking, the power abruptly went out."</item>
        <item>"...When the prince kissed the princess, she coughed up the bits of an apple stuck in her throat. The dwarfs cried out in happiness. Snow White and the prince walked through a flower-covered path and headed to their kingdom. Everyone lived happily ever after.

        Then there was the apple created from the witch's wrath and curse. It was also a part of herself. The apple that dropped from Snow White's hand after a single bite could never be happy. The apple, full of loneliness and hatred toward the princess, waited for the day it would rot away and return to the earth.

        Was it the enchantment, or was it the wrath which was bending the laws of nature? Even after enough time had passed for it to rot and allow its seed to bear fruit, the apple did not rot. In the meantime, one half of it was kicked and crushed by someone's foot, the other half was filled with holes, eaten away by the likes of birds and bugs.

        The carcasses of birds and bugs piled up near the apple. The apple pondered about its existence in the midst of the corpses rotting around it. One day, a branch grew from it. The leaves and branches were already withered and dry, but it continued to grow.

        Finally, one afternoon the apple gained the ability to move on its own. It thought of the princess and the prince who left happily. Snow White had also been sleeping for a long time, but a prince came and woke her up. The apple, now a princess in its own right, no longer needed a prince; she began to embark on a journey.
        - Excerpt from ‘The Hidden Stories in Fairy Tales No One Knew’ (Author unknown)"</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality that takes the form of a giant spider, guarding its domain in darkness. It's difficult to see the Abnormality with bare eyes. Small spiderlings skitter around the floor.
        Our proud employee, Peter, entered the Abnormality’s Containment Unit one day. When he shone the flashlight on the floor, small little spiders skittered away from the light.
        When Peter squashed one of the spiderlings by accident, a giant spider descended from the ceiling. Peter was dragged to the ceiling in only a moment. The cocooned employee hanging off the ceiling of the Containment Unit will be a healthy meal for the spider's offspring.
        Unsurprisingly, not a single employee volunteered to retrieve the corpse of their cocooned colleague.
        ...A fact often overlooked by many is that victims trapped in a spider's cocoon are actually not dead. The prey is in fact slowly dying within. Their death is postponed so they can be kept fresh for later consumption. A spider's poison contains a toxin that permanently damages the heart, eventually leading to death. Insects, trapped in the pitch-black cocoons, have no choice but to wait for the spiderlings to feed on them, feeling their heart beat slower and slower. (Omitted)

        We do appreciate your suggestion. However, our own research indicates that your concerns are unlikely to be true. Furthermore, it is proven that the presence of a cocoon in the Containment Unit increases the energy output. For these reasons, we will not implement a rescue procedure for employees who are caught by Spider Bud as it is against our interests. However, we will allocate more resources into researching this specimen in the future per your opinion. Please be advised that disrupting the atmosphere of our workspace by spreading unconfirmed rumors is against the code of conduct, and may even be subject to penalties including dismissal. Lobotomy always values the welfare and voices of its employees. - Head of the Welfare Department, Lobotomy Corporation.
        There's an eerie rumor spreading among employees. It's not out of the ordinary for a rumor or two to spread in a company like this, but it is interesting that the number of alleged witnesses seems to multiply.
        The rumor says the following: “Whispers can be heard in the Containment Unit at night...” “It was the voice of Alex, who went missing a few days ago...” “They say the voice wept in terror, asking to be saved from the darkness...”
        "</item>
        <item>"A self-loathing Abnormality that spends every day letting out miserable screams. It wishes to break the cycle of the curse, but there is no way to do so. Beauty was once a fair lady with charming green eyes. One day, this poor lady learns of a job opening at the manor of the count, with the promise of hefty payment.
        The count had a monstrous appearance. Rumor says anyone who dares to enter his manor is never seen again.
        'It must be that hideous monster preying on people.' With that thought in her mind, she brought a very sharp knife with her.
        The lady was hired and worked at the manor. Contrary to the rumor, the monster was nowhere to be seen. Sometimes at night, she could hear a voice. It was very kind and compensated her for her troubles handsomely.
        Working in the manor, the lady bore a greedy thought. 'If the count was gone, I could take all his possessions for myself!' '
        One day, she went inside the count's room. The room that she was instructed to never enter during the day. There she saw the count's true form. He was truly horrendous. Hundreds of eyes, four legs, he was neither human nor animal.
        The lady thought: 'Perhaps such a hideous monster would be better off if it didn't exist.' She proceeded to stab the beast with her knife.
        Surprisingly, the beast laughed in its last moments.
        Before the lady could even ask why it was laughing, she began to change. Hundreds of eyes formed and a thick coat of fur grew on her. Soon, she turned into the beast.
        Now, the manor and all its riches belonged to her.
        ...Rumor says anyone who dares to enter the count's manor is never seen again."</item>
        <item>"Wears a black fedora and a beaked mask. Has huge black wings instead of arms or legs. It is capable of human communication, though it prefers to talk little. It came to this facility by itself, claiming that the world has contracted a dreadful disease only it is able to cure. We could not find anything about this “disease” it refers to.
        It seems to like treating employees when they are injured or sick. It shows satisfaction when helping others, and it seems quite sympathetic and benevolent. Even after a week of observation, we found no aggression, violence, or attempt to escape. Only contributions to the assumption that this Abnormality is eminently “gentle” (12 of our employees used this word to describe this creature) and good for us.
        Employee Alex, who had a serious scar on his forehead from subduing an Abnormality, walked into this Abnormality's chamber with his scar's recovery incomplete. The Abnormality, which normally isn't loquacious, started talking as soon as it saw the employee's scar.
        Observation Record_1
        The Abnormality asked: “Why have you not treated that scar?”
        Alex replied: “I had no time, so I just gave it a little bit of first aid.”
        Then the Plague Doctor answered: “I shall heal you, curing you of all disease and injury you possess.”
        Alex came out of the chamber with his scar completely healed."</item>
        <item>"It takes the form of a newborn fetus, though the appearance is so grossly grotesque, it's hard to even call it a fetus. While communication is possible, it doesn't occur in a normal way. Every word He utters echoes throughout the entire Containment Unit.

        “My disciples, whom I blessed, ye shall leave the way of evil that once ye were following and find me. When the time comes, I shall forgive your sins and descend to the earth ye are living on.”

        The twelve employees who were blessed by Him will transform and roam the facility to deliver redemption to every single employee. Wings will grow from their backs, and they will wear masks in the shape of beaks and bear crosses that forgive all sins.

        “Follow my teachings as I told thee. Thou wilt abandon flesh and be born again.”

        His disciples will be born again as ones who shall reach out to those far away from the light, ones who shall embrace their neighbors, missionaries who shall spread the gospel to all their fellows. They are…

        “The time has come. Soon, the bell shall ring. A new world will come. Rise, my servants. Rise and serve me. I am death and life. Darkness and light.” "</item>
        <item>"A machine in the shape of a box with a tempting big red button. Old scribblings are written around it. They're mostly warnings, such as: Don't push the button.

        Many employees file their temptation to push the button as so strong it gives them insomnia. However, as the number of employees claiming they are suffering from this temptation is quite large, a solution to this problem is being worked on currently.

        One of the most important aspects of defining an abnormality is free will. This Abnormality is confirmed to possess a strong will to make anyone around it want to push it. Thus, it is categorized as an Abnormality.

        When the button is pressed, things that shouldn't happen, happen. Some say an apocalypse will befall, others say rainbow-colored light will shine down and unicorns will descend from the sky, and others still say a bomb buried deep underneath the facility will detonate and reset everything. However, none of these rumors are confirmed.

        Caution is advised as this Abnormality possesses the ability to evoke one's curiosity to press it. Sometimes, it changes its shape in a cunning attempt to be pressed by mistake.


        When I snapped back to reality, I was standing right in front of the containment room, just about to press that damn button. I would have, if not for the other employees dragging me out of that situation...

        The employee is currently back on duty after going through various tests and being diagnosed as normal. Although, we did order the employee to go to counseling, as they still visibly expressed dissatisfaction for missing the opportunity to press the button."</item>
        <item>"An Old Card attached to the Abnormality
        『Merry Christmas! Santa rushes along the night sky to deliver presents to happy kids who don’t cry. Rudolf, the red-nosed reindeer, shines his nose so bright through the fog while tugging along a sleigh full of presents, guiding it along tonight. Every happy kid around the world deserves a present!』

        From afar, the Abnormality resembles Santa Claus atop his sleigh, but upon closer inspection, it is completely different from its description in common folklore. Contrary to the titular character Rudolph, the sleigh drags the reindeer along. We’ve observed the three different portions of the Abnormality separately.

        Rudolph: An organic entity in colors of green, red, and white that appears to be a horse or a deer. Its muscles do not seem to move, but many of our staff report movement in the eyes. Some even say that they’ve made eye contact with it. There’s a 30cm diameter hole in its abdomen. Armed employees later reported that the hole was empty.

        Santa: A mysterious and transparent organic entity on top of Rudolph. It is full of what seems to be human organs, all of which function normally.

        The Sleigh: The size is similar to that of a child’s. The plating looks like organic skin, and there are white runners attached to the bottom. The accessories of the sleigh are replaced with stiff, severed hands. Unknown objects are carefully wrapped in gifts. Many employees tried to open these gifts but failed. Rumor has it that they can only be opened on Christmas Day.

        These three elements are crudely sewn together. Dr. ████████ suggested that “All three parts may be made from a single body. Whoever made this thing must have had a great hatred for Christmas. Well, that or they’ve never seen Santa Claus. "</item>
        <item>"Its form appears to be an amalgamation of a gargantuan beehive and a bee. A cross-section of the inside shows a darkish red surface with particles here and there, much like that of raw meat. The segment that appears to be the face is heavily distorted. It has wings, but they lost their intended function of flight. The one eye that remains relatively intact shows pupillary movement, as if to watch for approaching intruders. (The Abnormality always remains still, so it is assumed that it does not move.)
        When certain conditions are met, it releases spores. It will generate billions of spores within a 20-meter radius. The existence of lifeforms in its vicinity seems to be one of the key requirements.
        When it did, there was no immediate change in the employees who inhaled the spores, and no anomalous signs could be detected on the examinations that followed.
        Once more time had passed, the employee experienced severe pain in their occipital lobe and abdomen. Then after a certain period of time, their head dislodged from their body, and a Worker Bee emerged from the separated body.
        It has been confirmed that the spores carry drone eggs that hatch inside a living host. Based on the findings of an autopsy done on an employee killed by the Abnormality, we believe that the larva will subsist on any portion of the body, be it blood, organs, or fat. It will move freely around the body at this stage.
        When it becomes too large to move, it creates a cocoon near the intestines. The host feels extreme hunger at this stage, eating much more than usual. This cocoon moves upward through the body as it grows, eventually damaging the arteries of the throat and the cricothyroid with its jaws as it severs the host’s head from the body. After this it will emerge from the body, exacerbating the wound of the host further.

        ***** had been telling me about his itchy neck for a while. He complained about indigestion too; one time I saw him take a bunch of digestives. Who woulda thought that it’d turn out to be such a serious issue? I never knew I’d be the one to witness that horrible moment. (Omitted)
        ***** and I were just chatting, but suddenly he stopped speaking. He was still scratching his neck. It was turning so red, I was getting worried. Then his neck started to turn at such a strange angle.
        Right then and there I realized the severity of the situation. There was no way he could’ve been putting his neck that way on his own. It looked like someone was forcefully twisting his neck.
        And then, I heard a zip, like the noise of shredding paper, a foreign sound of something tearing. His head fell to the floor. I heard a dull thud.
        Then as if enough hadn't happened already, something began to crawl out of his neck. Just like a butterfly emerging from a cocoon, tearing apart his headless body; the wings, the yellow trunk, the teeth that gnawed away his body; it's something I never want to see again, a being I'd hate to describe as something alive...
        (Omitted) It seemed to be aware of me somehow. But it looked like it didn't have any reason to attack at that moment. It picked up his cranium and flew away, like a drone carrying honey...
        ...I can still hear the sound of its jaw rattling and its wings beating.
        Worker Bee
        Its appearance is clearly different from Queen Bee's, other than its color. It is capable of flight, but can only hover about 1 meter above the ground. It lacks antennae or eyes. A long appendage that appears to be an intestine drags behind its rear on the floor.
        Worker Bees show only two forms of behavior: Delivering nutrients to the Queen, and proliferating. Upon encountering an employee, it uses its jaw to crush their head and then proceeds to inject a pupa into their body."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality which contains the pain of all those who couldn’t take their sorrow in stride.
        A bath of a gloomy color, topped up with blood. The blood is always kept in equilibrium; it never overflows. Only despair can be found in its sunken depths. Unbearable depression overwhelms all who look into the bath. In an instant, it can pull a nearby person into it. It bears no considerable strength, but those who suffer from its crushing depression do not resist. It devours the victim until nothing remains except for their wrists. All the hands which float in the bath are pale, exsanguinated; they stretch into the air and reach out as if asking for help.
        It is no easy feat to cut one’s wrist with a sane mind. A strong will is needed with the resolve to make multiple attempts. Only when it is sliced as if one were simply cutting a mere slab of meat, can they achieve this. Only when one yearns for death that much, can they succeed.
        I eternally regret not realizing to ask her why she needed that industrial knife. I eternally regret not realizing that she was hiding her wrists with long sleeves. I eternally regret not realizing that she always took extra care to hide them whenever I spoke with her. I eternally regret not realizing that I never heard her cheerful laughter anymore, and that she roamed around the company with lifeless eyes more and more often.
        I can’t even imagine how painful it would be to cut your wrist. I found out that the only reason she could manage to do something like that was she cut hers straight through.
        We always popped open a bottle of wine every time we succeeded. It became one of our customs. She told us that it only takes one slight misstep to fall into indifferent habit if we get too used to success. Thus, we should always smile, rejoice, and celebrate every little thing in the wake of success. And we should never neglect failure, as success can be born from a pile of failures. When I saw the latticework of scars on her wrist, I was reminded of our wine cabinet. We had used up so many of the bottles; there was only one left. That day, I popped the cork off the last one."</item>
        <item>" Employees’ Records (Source Unknown):
        Hey have you guys ever been to one of those Lobotomy meetups?? Mind you, it took a lot of courage for me to bring this up again… You see, there’s a bunch of clubs in this company where employees gather up. I once attended some kinda ping-pong group event thing but there weren’t any girls there so I pulled out real quick lol.
        So like, one day I saw this announcement for some weird get-together on the corp message board. I got interested so I called up the group leader and he introduced himself as ***** from Safety.
        I asked if there were any girls in the group, and he told me there were a ton of female employees. Now that got me super interested so I signed up right away for the upcoming meetup. So I showed up, got a name tag like everyone else. I don’t remember everything, but I think I saw like three people from Training and two from Information.
        About maybe half an hour later, the leader brought in dozens of cans of WellCheers on a tray and gave one to each of us… I should have realized something was wrong cause the can was already opened, but I’m a sucker for soda and I just gulped the damn thing down my throat the moment he passed me a can lmaooo

        Now after that the leader told us it’s time to move, and he said he got a van rented for us. We all thought he was an awesome guy for that. I hopped in the van with two employees from the horde and one guy from the same dept as me.
        Leader said it was gunna take about an hour drive so we could just nap if we wanted, so we did. Weird thing was though, I went to sleep real fast, like real fast. Like, the moment I shut my eyes I was out like a light. I have insomnia but for whatever reason I fell asleep so fast then. Sigh...that was my big mistake.
        Anyways, I was sound asleep, but then I heard seagulls, and was like, Wtf??? Seagulls??????? Yeah, at first I thought it was someone’s phone alarm, but then I heard waves crashing. I was like, “man this is way too real to be a phone alarm,” so I opened my eyes to find myself……lying on a deck. I was on a goddamn boat, lmfao. AN ACTUAL, REAL-LIFE BOAT. I knew I was screwed the moment I saw shrimp hopping around. Sent chills down my spine. I wanted to believe it was all a dream but I swear that shrimp’s realistic flopping was a sobering sight. The realization crushed me like a hammer.
        And I was surrounded by people who looked like they were the crew. They were all beefed up, it felt like they’d put me back to sleep with force if I said something wrong. One slip and I’d be swimming with sharks.

        The crew was something around 10 people including the captain, boatswain, cook and all that. They all chuckled at me while I was spacing out. The guy who looked like the captain walked towards me and asked me about my height and weight. I asked him when the ship goes to port. He told me it’d be about a month but that I shouldn’t try and run away or anything cause they already made a deal with “my people”.
        I had no damn idea who “my people” were but I was too scared to ask. Then the other crew members called me over for lunch. They were making instant ramen, putting shrimp, crabs, clams, and all sorts of other stuff in it. They told me to stop acting like I was about to jump into the sea and to try their ramen. I said no at first, but they laughed at me again saying there weren’t any sleeping pills or stuff like that in it and gave me some anyway. A man’s gotta live, so I ate it. It tasted better than I expected it to.
        As soon as we finished lunch they told me they were going to teach me how to adjust the ropes. I pretty much gave up at that point, so I just simply answered “sure…”. All I could see anyways was these little islands that no one would have a chance at surviving on. For a month, I learned how to pull up fish traps, fill bait boxes, repair fishing nets, cook some ramen, get coffee, and all sorts of stuff.

        I kept getting better and I got to the point where I could prepare mackerel sashimi and fish stew for the crew. Everyone complimented it. Said I could open a restaurant with that stew. Later on, we went through a couple of typhoons. Them and I started forming some kind of bond. A companionship. Whales were becoming a common sight at that point. Two weeks in, the captain told me I was pretty good and asked me if I was interested in officially joining the crew. When I thought about it, I would have been fired from the Corp anyway, so this seemed like a legit opportunity to make a living. This was the first time I ever got a compliment after all.

        What am I doing now? Well, I’ve been promoted and now I’m living fine. I’ve found true happiness in cracking open a cold one after a hard day’s work, covered in sea water and sweat. I’m at the port now but we gotta take off soon to catch some more shrimp. Never know what your future holds, bros.
        Sometimes I think about those other folk who were at the meetup that day. Not that I really wanna snoop around to find out though, I just try to keep a positive mind. I wanna say they’re hopefully doing good just like me. Oh, it’s time to sail out, see you guys."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality that knows of spring’s genesis and autumn’s passing.

        Its surface is smooth as if it were ceramic. In the place where the Abnormality’s eyes should be, it is empty. The cracks and openings are instead filled with growing plants.

        Alriune, a lovely one; a doll yearned to be human. It was adored by people, its pupils soulful.
        Alriune, abandoned in a dark forest; its eyes stolen by crows lusting for glitter. Its mind, life, and heart slowly withered away.
        Alriune, lacking eyes but all-seeing; a human yearned to be a doll. Bearing the hope to return to dust, it shall go back to the grave with all that desires to live."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality whose brain is imbued with rage, screams, and malicious cries. There is a wound on his forehead that never seems to heal. He hates everyone and everything. He wears a straitjacket, but is as free as any man. No amount of chains and restraints is enough to prevent him from committing violence.
        He always had to wear a straitjacket. Some say he was a death row inmate from a federal prison. The researchers were always cautious around him. They felt that the straitjacket couldn't contain him. The researchers wanted to study a murderer's brain to prove that innate evil existed.
        It was difficult to determine who was worse: A man who murdered the innocent with no remorse, or the researchers who wanted to open up his brain to satiate their curiosity.
        A wide range of medicine and chemicals were injected into him. Some were used for the sake of humanity's future, while others were for new medical techniques. They all had the potential of changing the world. The researchers were getting more and more excited. Although they didn't openly express so, it was almost palpable.
        They said they found a cure, but they never said what was cured. The prisoner spoke less and less. His aggressiveness was suppressed, but at the same time, he lost himself. After an extensive review, he was permitted to have the straitjacket removed.
        “It feels like my head is turning into metal. I sometimes hear metallic creaks in my head...”
        As the days passed by, he began inflicting self-harm. He would continuously hit his head on the wall or hard surfaces. He insisted on checking if his head really was turning into metal. One day they eventually decided to leave him with the hope that he would stop once he was wounded. However, even with blood pouring down his face, he wouldn't stop until his wound was so deep the whites of his skull were peeking through. He had to wear the straitjacket again, but he was no longer feared or monitored like before.
        A researcher died. It would have been difficult to identify him without his ID card as his head was violently crushed. Lax security meant that the door was often left unlocked or unattended. The prisoner that everyone believed to be confined was moving around on his knees.
        “My head... turning into metal... folds in my brain, being flattened...” He kept repeating strange words, and the final procedure was quickly put in place. Treatment was halted, and he was dissected so his brain could be used for research. How do I know? I sedated him myself. He kept muttering nonsense until the end.
        “Ends, begins, ends, begins, end” "</item>
        <item>"It was a night veiled in gentle mist.
        A barefooted child was looking at me.
        I stopped, because I saw the sadness hanging on his face.
        He was crying, his dreamy eyes filled with sorrow.
        I gave him my help.
        The sadness hanging on his face stopped me in my tracks. He said he lost something precious, and when I offered to help, He gave me a big smile.
        A teardrop fell from the child's dewy eyes, as stars showered from the sky.
        The world falls into a slumber, trapped in an ecstatic lullaby.
        That night the galaxy descended with bare feet.
        - Excerpt from the diary of Employee *****, who committed suicide.
        It takes the form of a young boy with big eyes and skin that resembles the night sky.
        The child shows great enjoyment with talking and playing with others. He has a strong attachment to the act of making contact with another.
        If the child and an employee reach a certain level of intimacy, he will give a small pebble to the employee he now considers his friend. The employee will feel happiness and vigor while in possession of the pebble. However, this pebble will do more than just good if the employee happens to enter any Containment Unit other than his.
        If an employee in possession of one of the child’s pebbles (the sign of their strong friendship) dies, he will show deep grief and sorrow for their loss.
        Excerpt from Employee *****'s Diary:
        X/X/XX
        I looked into the child's eyes for a while. I may have spaced out a little bit because his eyes were so dreamy. I wanted to pet him, but I remembered my coworkers telling me not to have personal feelings towards Abnormalities.
        X/X/XX
        I told him my name. He repeated it with wide eyes as if he found out a big secret. Each time he called my name, it felt like it became something more than just a familiar thing I had been living with.
        X/X/XX
        When another employee entered the child's Containment Unit, he did not follow that employee and looked for me instead. I felt basely triumphant after hearing about that. The kid follows me, not you.
        X/X/XX
        The moment I entered the child's room, he jumped into my arms crying. When I finally set him down, he shed a tear that became a small, white pebble that fell in my hand. Please don't lose it, and don't give it to anyone else. The boy mumbled.
        X/X/XX
        Do you like it? More than you like me? The boy quietly asked when I arrived after finishing working with another Abnormality. I asked how he knew what I was doing, and he answered lightly: Isn't it obvious? I know everything. Whatever you do, wherever you go. His gaze lay on the pebble, then he smiled. His eyes gave me goosebumps.
        X/X/XX
        I tried to rid myself of the pebble, but I realized it was beyond my control. I don't get what I'm talking about right now but... You still treasure it right? The child smiles at me. Smiles. Smiles. Smiles. Smiles...
        X/X/XX
        I can't get this pebble off me. My only hope is to wait for the child to tire of me. I'm waiting for that day... but will it ever come? (People tell me I’m an excellent employee. Idiots, they don’t know a thing. Shut up.)
        X/X/XX
        I can't take it anymore. I can't escape him. I thought I was in charge, but the truth is I was just a pebble in his hands the whole time. Whatever I do, wherever I go, I hear his whispers. (I have to end it, but I’m not even sure if I can.)
         ...I came from afar. I'm so glad to meet you. Become a pebble, and let's walk the galaxy together... I hear his whispers and breath. Pitch black darkness follows... just like the night I met him."</item>
        <item>"A small and confident bird that punishes the evil, guilty, and all sorts of irreverent people. Some employees have said that it is cute when the bird mightily flutters its tiny wings.
        People have been committing sins since long ago. Why do they commit sins, knowing it's wrong? The small bird wondered. “It must be because there's no one to punish people for their misdeeds. If someone takes that role, then no foul act would happen in this world ever again!” With this in mind, the little bird left the forest it had been living in, and never went back."</item>
        <item>"I'm a pro. If you make a request, then I might help you. I used to be expensive, but I'll cut you some slack here, under one condition. Hand that dreadful, cunning bastard over to me if you ever see him. I’ll hang his head over my bed. Only then can I get up in the morning without having a nightmare.”
        An imposing Abnormality taking the form of a female warrior with a striking red hood. Her frayed hood has initials embroidered on it, unreadable due to the damage the hood has taken. Many patches can be seen on the hood, suggesting that it's been well-worn. According to her own claims, she used to be a mercenary before coming to this facility, wandering around without fixed residence. She does not trust others easily, and has an extreme fondness for battle.
        She is unusually uncomfortable with parts of her face and body being exposed, or looking at a mirror. Other numerous symptoms of paranoia have been observed in her behavior. She has a strong desire to resolve emergency situations when they break out. She calls it “a request” of some kind. Since this behavior consequently helps management, the company recommended putting it to use depending on the situation.
        ※ The following contains information that employees of every level should note.
        However, when she encounters the “Big Bad Wolf”, the situation will change drastically. She will undergo several psychological transitions including sudden depersonalization and intermittent explosive disorder. This encounter will lead to serious collateral damage, so it is advised to avoid any case where the two may face each other.
        Between us, there's no victory to be won. All I think about is how I'll kill that bastard in a way more gruesome and painful than the last time. Thus, there's no toasts to raise. There's no deliciously baked cakes to eat, or wine to drink. I got used to grinding the axe instead of picking flowers when I was 15.” "</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality in the shape of a wolf with sparsely damaged fur. It is bipedal, and is capable of communication to some extent. It always attempts to devour employees or breach. Such actions are easily preventable, since it shows obvious signs in behaviour and conversation before doing so, making this Abnormality fairly easy to manage.

        The incident on the day of ***** was an alerting event for many employees. The moment Red Riding Hood ran into the Wolf, the situation spiraled out of control. Prevent the two from meeting at all costs. Considering the potential damage it may cause, it could be a wise decision to sacrifice a few employees to divert their attention away from each other.

        He had flesh for the first time in a long while, and its taste was so good. In the corner of his eye, a familiar piece of red cloth stood out from the wardrobe. He may or may not have seen it before, but he didn't really care about it. Since then, it got harder and harder to keep himself in check. Still, it didn’t matter to him. After all, he was “destined” to be a big bad wolf.

        There may be lots of stories here, but no story is as disgusting as the wolf's role. It was a sin to be born as a wolf. No one cared about a wolf's name. It has to be called the big bad wolf. All wolves are raised to become giant, ferocious, and hairy monsters. Wolves could not eat other animals even if they were starving. Wolves could not cross the line when doing bad things. And wolves had to be punished. Wolves always needed to be an example. Wolves could not make friends with anyone... (Omitted)"</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality that resembles a child's innocent doodles. Originally, it had no stable form, its shape would continually morph. To this day its aspects still change, albeit at a much slower pace. Component analysis has revealed that the Abnormality consists of matter that does not exist on Earth. It is notable for its metaphysical appearance that one cannot explain with words.
        It often shows incomprehensible linguistic activity. One employee tried to decipher its speech (see Document #1 Employee David’s Song), but their mental contamination level rose beyond the limit within several days. They suffered severe psychosis and had to be quarantined.
        The Abnormality's tentacles (which are quite different from what we consider the average tentacle; for simplicity’s sake we’ve monickered them as “tentacles”) can pierce through the barrier of humanity. Employees impaled by the tentacles will suffer semi-permanent brain damage.
        When the Abnormality escapes its Containment Unit, it will emit noises in the corridor. As the sounds it makes have what could be considered a melody and syllables, we consider it “singing”. However, none of our staff can precisely remember it, given that most of the time they are unable to describe it due to their serious brain damage. Those who were within 100 meters of the “singing” called it a sound unheard of in this world. Because of these descriptions, we’ve titled it “Echoes from the Beyond”. (See Document #2 Singing)
        Experiment_1 The Possibility of Communication
        We have determined that the Abnormality has an intelligence similar to (or even higher than) that of humans, and gave it a simple language learning course. As a result, a crude communication by combining words has become possible. The following is a segment of the communication record with the Abnormality.

        Q: Are all of your kind similar in appearance?
        A: Negative. Outside. Child. See. Picture. Face. Happy. Change. Form.

        Q: Why have you come here?
        A: Knowledge. Share. Human.

        Q: Why do you want to share your knowledge with us?
        A: Understanding. Knowledge. Moment. Know. Universe. Coincidence. Negative; None.

        This section is an attempt to decipher the conversation with the Abnormality.
        1. It based its form on a picture drawn by a child. It changed its form because the child's expression while drawing it was happy.
        2. It came here to share its species’ knowledge with us. The moment we fully understand that knowledge, we will know their ultimate goal.
        3. There is no such thing as a coincidence in the universe.
        Experiment_2 An Experiment on Laughter
        After watching a video about laughing for 30 minutes, the Abnormality understood the concept of “laughing”. After that, when employees entered its Containment Unit to work with it, it would sometimes emit a strange noise with what appeared to be the shape of a smile on its face. It looked like it was mimicking laughter.
        Experiment_3 Comprehension of Symbols
        We taught it the meaning of various symbols along with language. Among them was the shape of a heart. This symbol provoked a distinct change from the Abnormality.

        Q (Showing the Abnormality a picture of a heart): This is the symbol of the “heart”. Many people believe that emotions come from the heart, and this symbol is used to express positive emotions or a liking towards someone. (Omitted)

        Afterwards, several symbols resembling hearts were seen on the Abnormality’s body. It seemed to understand that the symbol could be used to express friendliness towards humans. Combining the results of the previous two experiments, we can confirm that this Abnormality is non-hostile to humans, and wishes to become friends.
        Document #1 Employee David’s Song
        David was famous in his department for his attempts to communicate with the 'Fragment of the Universe'. He was an intellectual who enjoyed reading philosophical books and gazing at the stars. He held interest in the Abnormality and as such he got the job; he researched its language and behaviour purely out of personal interest.
        So what became of David? Eventually, he succeeded in entering the domain of the Fragment of the Universe. However, it was obvious that his small brain couldn't withstand it. He was transferred to the psychiatric ward, and died of starvation while singing an unrecognizable song. This is why the Abnormality’s voice cannot be revealed to the public.
        Audio Record: Echoes in the Universe (Currently Removed)
        Document #2 Singing
        ...Why didn't you tell me earlier that the Abnormality was responsible for their condition? I have no idea if there’s any pattern, but they all show the same strange behavior on the exact same days. Can you imagine a group of patients staring at the sky with dazed faces, wailing strange noises in the corridor at night while everyone is asleep? I had such a difficult time persuading the other patients that they must have been practicing for the company’s upcoming Halloween event. Psychiatric treatment and medicine won't help.
        Coming, coming, still coming, they keep repeating these words, and anything else they utter is not from any language we know. I think sending them to a general hospital was an unwise decision.
        -Doctor from the (Record Deleted) Ward."</item>
        <item>"An armor that seems to have been used hundreds of years ago. An engraving on its bottom states: “Life is only granted to those who hold no fear of death.” Obviously, putting this armor on is forbidden by the company regulations.
        Note: There have been rumors of employees pretending to put on the armor for fun. Please look into this immediately!
        This armor was secured from a museum. The information below is the fragments of its legend.
        …This armor once belonged to General XXXX, who joined the War of XX during the year of XXX. It was a family heirloom, passed down through many generations. The general always wore this armor to keep himself protected. By a stroke of bad luck however, an arrow flew into a gap in the armor, killing him instantly. Somehow, the armor was undamaged.
        After the death of General XXXX, the armor was presented to Commander XXX of Battalion 00. The commander was always seen steel-clad each time he set out into battle. During one of his battles, the commander fell from his horse while fleeing from the enemy and died due to a fatal injury upon his skull. Still, the armor once again remained undamaged. There are many others throughout this armor’s history who have had their hands on it, and each and every one of them has died in battle. Meanwhile, the armor still kept its pristine condition.
        Over the years, the armor made its way to a warrior named XXX. He was known for simply keeping the armor in storage, not wearing it for a single battle. Eventually, XXX died of old age after participating in dozens of wars without sustaining a single injury. During his lifetime, the armor’s right arm became damaged, but there was no sign of exterior impact. XXX’s family later donated the armor to a museum.
        After running a few tests on the armor, we have come up with the following conclusions: If this armor is worn by a cowardly employee, their chances of fatal injury and death are drastically increased. Inversely, when an employee who holds no fear of death wears it, their chances of injury and death are exceedingly decreased.
        One of our personnel managers suggested an entrance test where interviewees wear the armor and walk around in it for ten minutes. This suggestion was immediately shot down."</item>
        <item>"A bird that used to judge the living in the dark forest, carrying around an unbalanced scale.

        The scale always tilts the same direction, but it doesn't know this as its eyes are covered. Or perhaps it's turning a blind eye to this truth.

        In fact, the bird was once an even-handed justiciar. Its scale would never neglect the weight of even the smallest sin. The long bird made a scale that was capable of weighing any sin to maintain the peace of the forest.

        At one point, the bird's eyes could see through anything. The eyes always shone brilliantly, burning like stars in the night sky. But it gave its eyes to the Big Bird in order to protect the forest. Now, only the void fills its eye sockets. The bandage is in tatters, like it could tear off at any second. The bird's face was once covered in gleaming feathers, but they fell out as it spent too much time without sunlight.

        All that remains is the unjust scale. The long bird continues on, doling out judgement."</item>
        <item>"Known to come when the world is filled with sin, many employees fear the advent of this Abnormality.

        To talk about this bird, we first need to tell the story of the Black Forest. We must remember the forest that was once so peaceful and beautiful…

        And the apocalypse shall follow.

        The Tale of the Black Forest

        Once upon a time, three happy birds lived in a warm and lush forest.

        The birds had no names, though the creatures of the forest would call them Big Bird, Long Bird, and Small Bird.

        Everyone lived freely and happily together in the peaceful forest. The birds wanted the forest to be safe more than anyone else, that way creatures from the outside could visit and have fun.

        It was a warm and sunny afternoon when a stranger visited the peaceful forest. He was a traveler, pioneer, and prophet, but at the same time, he was a nobody. He wanted to enter the forest, but the birds found him suspicious, so they didn't let him in. The stranger, angered, told the birds as he left:

        “Soon, a tragedy will befall the forest. It will be tainted with misdeeds and evil, and there will be constant conflict. The tragedies will only stop when a terrible beast appears and devours everything. The sun and moon will shine upon the forest no longer; the forest will never go back to what it was before.”

        The birds worried about the prophecy. What if conflicts really break out and a beast shows up to harm the forest just like the man said? That's when the birds decided to become the guardians of the forest. They loved this forest more than anyone else did, so they wanted to protect the creatures living in the forest and keep the peace.

        Big Bird, with its many eyes, decided to watch over the forest for intruders. For Big Bird's eyes could see very far, and see things we cannot see. Then somebody said, “But what if the beast shows up in the middle of the night, when the sky is dark and everyone is asleep?” Worried, Big Bird burned all of its feathers to make an everlasting lamp. Now the creatures of the forest were under Big Bird's constant watch, day and night.

        To keep the forest's peace, Long Bird weighed the sins of those who entered the forest. For Long Bird's scale was fair and just, and could weigh any and all kinds of sin. Then somebody said, “But what if the scale doesn't tip in either direction someday?” Worried, Long Bird made a scale that always tipped to one side. That way every judgement would yield a clear verdict.

        Small Bird decided to punish the creatures' wrongdoings with its beak. Then somebody said, “But your beak is so small, no one would find it hurtful.” Worried, Small Bird tore its mouth wide so it could swallow any creature in one bite.

        No one could visit the forest anymore, and bad rumors about the forest began to spread outside. “I heard terrible things happen to any creature that enters the forest.”

        “The Big Bird is always watching the creatures of the forest, there's no freedom.”
        “The Long Bird's scale isn't fair at all.”
        “The Small Bird's punishment is so scary.”
        The birds got upset. “We work so hard to protect the forest; why doesn't anyone appreciate our effort?”

        Fewer and fewer visitors came to the forest, more and more creatures were complaining, fights broke out daily, and yet the birds continued to work even harder to make the forest peaceful again, but...

        “No, this forest is so vast and wide, the three of us aren't enough to protect all of it.”
        “But there is no creature to protect this forest but us.”
        “If we combined our power, we could be stronger.”
        The day when Big Bird's eyes that could see hundreds of kilometers away, Long Bird who could judge any sin, and Small Bird's mouth that could devour everything united into one, darkness fell upon the forest. Creatures screamed in terror and fear at the sight of the bird, and the forest soon fell into mayhem.

        Then, in the middle of all the chaotic cries, someone shouted:

        “It's the beast! A big, scary monster lives in the black, dusky forest!”

        The beast is here? The three birds, now as one, looked around but there was no one to be seen. The bird began to prowl the forest, looking for the monster. The forest would be in trouble if the beast really showed up.

        But there was nothing. There were no creatures, no sun and moon, and no beast. All that was left was just a bird and the Black Forest.

        Since then, there were only nights dark as pitch.

        Rumors say that there is a terrible beast in the Black Forest where no one lives.

        Survivor Testimony

        Every single light in the facility went crazy. They kept flickering and flickering. I couldn’t even use my lighter. Then, this warm light shone through it all. It looked like a waning twilight, or a growing sunrise. Though, as we all know, sunlight can’t make its way into our facility. Everyone silently gazed at the light. Sudden darkness and a weird ray of light were enough reason to be frightened. It was scarier than anything gorey we’d seen here. It was a true fear of the unknown itself…

        (Omitted) …Something from afar was coming our way. Incandescent lights like stars from outer space were marching towards us. It looked like Big Bird’s eyes, but it wasn’t that Abnormality. I could hear these long arms scratching the floor.

        Someone broke the silence with a whisper: “That guy over there couldn’t run away in time...”

        There was an employee kneeling on the floor; perhaps he couldn’t sense the danger approaching behind him, and once he noticed, it was too late. He couldn’t even scream. Nobody would have been able to then. He just meaninglessly struggled to move his legs, desperate to run from the beast. There was no heroic act of someone standing up against the monster, not even a yell to warn him. Everyone was just watching him, waiting for the terrible thing that was about to happen.

        Each step sent a tremor through the whole facility. The monster was moving with such slow steps, but it seemed so fast.

        In the blink of an eye, it devoured the nameless employee in one bite, and right after that everyone started screaming in chaos. I had gone through handling countless suppressions, but that day, for the first time, I regretted ever joining the company. I was certain I wouldn’t get out of there alive. This helplessness overwhelmed me. I couldn’t even think about fighting back against the monster, and many others were feeling the same.

        I think I’m the only one who stayed sane enough to write this among all the survivors. The company will never tell our newbies about the existence of that monster. However, I wanted to leave them a warning at the very least. That’s why I’m writing this."</item>
        <item>"The first bit of humanity's desire started with the bite of a sweet apple. We've been banished from Eden for that sin. And now we're standing inside a vast orchard. My basket is so large, all the fruits of the world can't make it full. But, is it so bad to lust for honey when there are flowers? After all, we are born to pursue happiness.
        Happiness became obsession, obsession became greed, and the greed forever solidified to become a golden amber. The happiness in the beginning, still holding a smile, dwells inside.
        The first seed of desire originated from the pure yearning for happiness. The tiny seed grew larger and larger, hungering for more. Over time, the seed hardened and turned into a piece of shiny gem. Enticed by its sheen, a starving fish swallowed it. But it only made the fish even hungrier.
        The desires of people usually go unfulfilled. Many desires are abandoned, but they are not completely gone. They hide deep in the subconscious, lurking at the bottom of the lake, ready to spring up at any moment.
        However, the yearning for happiness may also rear its head from time to time, darting its tongue like a snake. As soon as a tiny piece of bait falls into the river, the hungry fish will come up and snatch it in an instant.
        We delude ourselves to be highly rational beings who are in full control of these things, but it's such a preposterous belief, it's laughable. We don't have as much control over ourselves as we believe.
        The magical girl, who was no longer a magical girl, ate many things. Authority, money, fame, and many other forms of pleasure. She ended up eating away anything in her sight. Now, only visceral greed remains.
        Someone’s Diary
        Many people have secretly wished for a hero.
        They say there once was something called soul therapy. What does it feel like to have an ill soul? We are all healthy. But maybe all of this is a tragic illusion. Once, there were people who tried to change the world. We all remember them. We remember how they met their downfall.
        Desires, I know of desires that ruin all things. We no longer believe in something, nor do we entertain a hope for a miracle. We don't think too much about why they've changed. And we don't blame them. For we have realized that endless desire brings despair.
        I sometimes feel a terrible dejection, but I do not know where the pain comes from. ...Many people have secretly wished for a hero.
        Deep is the sorrow of the world. Greed—deeper still than agony. Sadness says: 'Begone, pass away!' But greed seeks eternity—seeks deep, deep eternity."</item>
        <item>"Among the employees, it was originally referred to as the ‘Giant Mushroom Chunk.’ It does appear to be a gigantic mushroom, and it bears some semblance to mold as well; overall, its appearance closely resembles fungi. It continuously releases spores into the air, visible to the naked eye.

        A majority of our employees are not fond of this Abnormality. Few are broad-minded enough to favor working with some giant mushroom that fills up half a Containment Unit, spewing out unknown spores; they have dozens of other things to worry about, including other Abnormalities to work with.

        As so few of our employees willingly volunteered to work with it, we could only record the most bare-bones information. Originally we utilized a shift system to designate what Abnormalities our staff were to work with. However, after the “Magical Girl Incident” a few years ago, we began to give consideration to the opinions of our employees when assigning work.

        The Abnormality produces motile, microscopic airborne spores. They mostly proliferate by invading other organisms through their respiratory systems. It is difficult to notice the initial symptoms from this invasion because the only sensations are a light dyspnea and dry, sandy throat. Thus, it is mandatory to wear a mask when working with this Abnormality.

        When an employee inhales enough spores, bizarre cysts will begin to grow on their body, and tissues will be eroded. Ultimately, they will become a dysmorphic creature whose original form is hardly noticeable. They will show hostility in this state, so they must be terminated on sight.


        There was this one guy who was awfully quiet. He was that guy who’d glance sideways at us like some kinda fox, as if he was expecting us to talk to him. One peculiar thing about him was that he would volunteer to work on the mushroom chunk, an Abnormality everyone loathed to visit. It was also disturbing that he would spend an unusually long time in its Containment Unit. Who knows what kind of monstrosity might have grown on his body?

        When we decided to call the Abnormality the Giant Mushroom Chunk among ourselves, that guy spoke up for the first time. Saying he's the one who's seen it the most. He talked a lot of nonsense, like how it didn't deserve to be called a mushroom chunk. Everyone laughed at him. We decided he finally had gone bonkers when he started saying stuff about how he became friends with the damn thing. I mean, it’s a common enough thing around here, lots of stuff happens.

        One person going insane isn’t a big deal. We tried to give him a couple hints to take a psychiatric test but he just gave us this condescending look like he knew something we didn’t. And a few days later, he kicked the bucket, as we all know. Did I mention that it was me who recognized him in that spore-mold-creature's carcass? The birthmark on his forehead. If we hadn't found that birthmark on that lump of spores, we'd never have even guessed it was him. No one actually knew he had a birthmark except me. Since, you know, no one in the department was friends with him.

        After becoming that monster, he just wandered around near the mushroom’s Containment Unit. We tried to lure him somewhere less crowded ‘cause he was attacking everything in sight. But he wouldn’t move more than ten meters away from the chunk until he died.

        This is why we decided to rename the Abnormality. Complex reasons, like pity for the guy who became friends with a mushroom of all things, and the remembrance of his tragic death. To tell you the truth, he needed a friend. That's why he let himself get infected, going crazy in hallucinations, not knowing that he was turning into a monster. The mushroom, it tamed the poor bastard simply to reproduce; it got Alex, whose name wasn't known by anyone...


        Employee Alex's notes
        The human mind is too fragile to visualize something in its truest form. Did you know that mantis shrimp can see hundreds of colors that humans cannot? That simple fact is enough of an example to illustrate my point that it’s detrimental to believe and judge everything by relying solely on what you see.

        I don’t actually have many friends. Don’t misunderstand me now. I don’t want to make a friend, I choose not to make friends; it’s not that I can’t. It is because we don’t understand each other. A person thinks of himself as a completely isolated entity, making it impossible to fully understand others. But ironically, an inherent instinct of mob psychology has survived over the course of our evolution. We repeatedly play a game of risk, walking a tightrope, vainly trying to understand each other while staying out of our territories. In fact, I was long done with this pointless game.

        I volunteered to observe the giant mushroom for a similar cause. No one wanted to get close to that Abnormality. It must be because of some petty reasons such as how it looks disgusting to their eyes. The fact that its appearance was slightly alien wasn't going to stop me. In fact, I actually felt a bit superior when everyone seemed surprised when I said I would work with it. (Omitted)

        The Abnormality didn't show any notable activity. I recorded and observed the silence with patience. One day, after it spread powders of enchanting colors, I experienced a special change. I could perceive hyper-reality, a plane higher than reality. This was a hand He gave to me.

        I took it and was rewarded with the invitation to such a special place. It was something only I could achieve. He talked to me telepathically. He welcomed me because I was the only one who could realize His essence. I had been imagining, yearning for the moment to converse through my mind. To be completely understood; the feeling of unification. It was so exhilarating, I could barely hide my joy. (Omitted)

        I wanted to get closer to Him. I wanted to be a part of Him. I always thought of Him. I wanted to belong to Him and understand His world. Like a flower bud about to bloom, my mind was pervaded... I was being tamed, little by little....



        This is a part of the footage caught by a surveillance camera in the Containment Unit. As the Abnormality's spores completely obscured the visual feed, only the audio could be extracted.

        Judging from the content of the recorded conversation, we deemed it safe to assume that the Abnormality's spores contain hallucinatory agents. Because even after a thorough analysis of the audio record, no voice other than the employee's could be detected. The employee, infected by the spores, suffered a severe state of frenzy before being shot down by another employee on the spot.

        - No, I don’t have any friends. Like I said before, I’m not fond of such contradictory relationships. At the very least, I think you could be my friend. The human language is too simple to illustrate this relationship, but I think we could settle on friends.
        - … Yes, I am your one and only friend.
        - I shall accept you. My life has been changed ever since I met you. I had been living my whole life feeling depressed, without a sense of purpose, without talking to anyone, just working all day. But you redeemed me, a person who abandoned oneself. Just like how I could perceive your true essence, you saw through mine.
        It is a truly rapturous experience. I'd like to understand you; I'd like to become a being like you and love you. I was born human, lived a tedious life and might have kept doing so had it not been for you. I was so happy that I met you.
        - Please remember me; please remember the nameless flower that bloomed just for you.
        - Even if this turns to be a curse, I will love this curse like a blessing. I will think about you to the day my mind collapses and crumbles. I will close my eyes thinking only of my sole friend who came from the far away universe…

        (Afterward, a faint sound of air leaking from the Abnormality could be heard before all fell silent)"</item>
        <item>"Similar to a child in size, and always maintaining a bright smile…
        A very very adoooorable little kid.
        They call me an adorable little kid because I am a small and lovely child!
        The kid comes from a place far far away!
        And when the kid meets someone she likes, she will give them a gift made all by herself.
        The gift's content is a secret though!
        This is another really really important secret, but the kid has lots of talents!
        This girl has many friends, but they said she can't bring them here.
        She was so sad that she had to leave her dear friends behind, so she came up with a brilliant idea!
        If I cover up my friends nicely and make it look like a gift, everyone will be surprised!
        And they'll all laugh together over my prank!
        Whoops, there goes the secret of the gift.
        I hope to find lots of friends here too!
        The kid is shy, so the gift will be given in secret!
        Farewells are sad, I hope we can play more!
        And people here don't smile!
        That looks so gloomy!
        So this little lady has made a decision! To stay here and never leave until laughter is restored to this place!
        I will be happy if everyone is pleased with my pranks!"</item>
        <item>"Where does one go when they die?
        Where did all the employees who worked here go?
        - They must have returned home. To a haven where family and warmth await.
        The employees cannot leave; once they join the company, the only way to leave is to resign.
        - Then those resigned employees must have returned home, having earned what they wanted and being full of hope.
        We are the feathers of a Wing. Resignation isn't as simple as you think. Just like how a feather doesn't detach from a wing of its own will.
        - Then, where did all the resigned employees go?
        They're bound to the company the moment they enter. Even if they do resign, they are doomed to stay here forever.
        - Long ago, in some world, people believe that they would become beautiful beings with small wings when they died. It's a silly story. Nonsensical too.
        If we get wings, will we be able to leave this place? Do we get our wings only after we retire?
        They say the mourner with a huge luggage on his back had come to be a savior to all. Eventually, he himself was trapped in this place, and now he wanders the company with only the memory of an empty faith. He's carrying a coffin. A large coffin to pay tribute to the employees who have nowhere else to go. However, it is still too small to comfort those innocent sacrifices.
        Inside it is a kaleidoscope of butterflies waiting for the moment to fall asleep. Until then, they flutter their wings uselessly. The wings that may have been many jumbled into one, or one split into many. Butterflies are supposed to pollinate flowers, but not a single proper flower blooms in this place. There is no choice but to wait. After all, there must be an end to every world."</item>
        <item>"The Devil ultimately wished for despair.
        For despair wears down the mind and drains one's will to go forward. When one feels there's nothing left to go for, their soul falls down to Hell, the Devil's domain. This is why the Devil finds it more entertaining to watch people fall to despair, rather than to simply kill them. We describe it as selling one's soul to the Devil.
        When a marksman received a gun from the Devil, the Devil proposed a childish contract: The last bullet would puncture the head of his beloved. The moment he heard that, he sought and shot all the people he loved. Then he told the Devil, This magical bullet can truly hit anyone just like you say.
        With the last bullet gone for good, the hunter traveled to numerous worlds. Sometimes he helped those in need or fought evil, but it was all done on impulse, not a gesture of goodwill or ideals. In one world, he was called a righteous hunter, while in another, he was a bloodstained gunman.
        One day, the marksman realized the Devil no longer followed him. He pondered why, then realized that his soul had already fallen to Hell from the beginning. The contract had already been fulfilled, so the Devil had left.
        The marksman, now a devil himself, continues to pull the trigger to gather the souls of others. Just as the Devil said, the bullets will puncture anything you please. Forever."</item>
        <item>"Elijah had a large family to provide for.

        Her impoverished parents would always say: “Although we don't have anything to pass onto you, we have the most valuable treasure, honesty and diligence. These may not be of great help to you now, but they will make all of you happy someday.”

        One day, a dense fog covered the city.
        The hazy fog, thought to be a natural phenomenon at first, didn't dissipate even after a few days had passed. Some claimed it was making them feel nauseous or making them retch, but most people thought nothing of it. A lot of people continued to work and go about their days in the fog.
        Of course, Elijah was one of the people who had to be okay with it. She was the only family member with a proper job, and the inheritance of poverty had left them in huge debt. Elijah had several brothers, but their wills were broken after being faced with several failures. Elijah was always tired, but she thought if she just worked a little harder, things would work themselves out. Just like what her parents used to say to her, and just like in fairy tales.
        Just like that bird who eventually spread its white wings and became the envy of all.

        Some people left the city to escape the fog. They said the city was done for. Elijah didn't listen. Elijah felt queasy at times. She felt her whole body blistering.
        Almost there, just a little more; if she held out just a little longer, the clothes made of nettles would be complete, and if she threw them to her brothers she once loved dearly, then the days when her family lived harmoniously could be restored.

        One day, on the way home after work, she bumped into a pedestrian running at full speed. Though the pedestrian who crashed into her was at a full sprint, he was unable to get back up, so she offered him a helping hand, asking if he was alright. He slapped her hand away and got up on his own. The pedestrian took a few faltering steps before collapsing again. The man seemed like he was running away from something; he seemed worried that Elijah would hurt him. Elijah tried to ask him what was wrong.

        However, the pedestrian opened his mouth first. The simple act of opening his mouth seemed labored, so she patiently waited for him to talk. The pedestrian didn’t open his mouth to speak; he began to vomit a mixture of blood and waste.
        The gooey mixture poured from his mouth at first, then it gushed out from his nose, ears, and eyes. If he hadn’t been expelling from all of his orifices, then Elijah might have tried to help him. Elijah thought she heard a shout in the distance. She left the vomiting man behind and started to walk slowly.

        What happens when the black swan wakes up from dreaming of a white swan?
        There were many people amidst the fog. Some screaming, some laughing. Some wielding clubs, some curled up; bodies covered in wounds. Dark, wet, and fetid dregs were scattered all over the ground, covered in footprints.
        She began to look for her brothers. Her family who needed to wear the nettle clothing to be free from the curse. Ones whom she shared happy dreams with. She saw her dear brothers in the distance. Elijah fell to her knees and finally started to puke up the thing everyone else was vomiting.
        The lake ripples gently. As if a number of swans just took flight."</item>
        <item>" “Just... Just keep showing him the book. Oh, and it has to be a page with pictures, since he probably can't read. When the experiment seems to drag on, try to draw his attention, like mimicking sounds. I don't need to explain every detail, right?

        Yes, I know. It's unfortunate. Pitiful and sad. I do feel human emotions, thank you very much. However, he ultimately survived thanks to this place. I hope he continues to live, in any shape or form. If you're thinking the same thing, it'd be better off if you dropped that guilt right now.
        ....
        Tell the kid today's treat is going to be grape-flavored candy. It's his favorite.”




        Contrary to popular belief, most sharks are small in size. There are only a handful of species that cause harm to humans... After all is said and done, the biggest appeal of sharks is their strong jaws and teeth. A shark's jaw can apply an intense amount of force, around 20 times that of an adult human. Besides, their vision and olfactory sense are extremely well developed, allowing them to locate their targets easily. This is why sharks could reign as the ocean's greatest predator until today.


        The parents had long deserted the child. They said the old infection would kill the child before two years passed. The researchers were the child's new parents. He learned to coo and walk. Although unable to talk properly, the child liked the ocean. Instead of visiting the ocean, the child was given candy which let him see the ocean. Many colorful nights and days passed.


        The child, who was thought to die within 2 years, managed to live for a long time. As always, he liked sweet candy, followed them, and loved the place as his home. Though the only thing the child could do was run around inside a cramped lab instead of a grass field under the sun, his steps were shaky but filled with enthusiasm. Excited about what kind of candy he would eat tomorrow."</item>
        <item>"A thorny Abnormality that feeds on the gaze of others and sometimes stretches its wings.
        Don't look away, just keep your eyes on it.
        It lives inside your gaze.
        The containment is but a facade.
        Contain it in your sight.
        Blinking is okay.
        It will tolerate such a brief moment of disruption.
        However, once it recognizes that it lost your attention and focus…
        It will spread its wings. Yes, wings.
        As if to praise a long-forgotten god, its lean, bloody wings will stretch and cover the whole corridor.
        The wings still bear fruit, using fresh corpses as food.
        If it still fails to gain your attention, the stalks will pierce the facility and grow toward a sunny spot.
        Like an angel, its wings will reach the skies and extend toward the ground, eventually blocking the sun out.
        But there is still hope.
        When you finally turn your eyes and bring it within your cognizance…
        It will return to this deep, dark subterranean area.
        That is, if you managed to survive by then.
        That's what a gaze is. Attention.
        An invisible string that connects us.
        Sole focus.
        Do not come here, as there is no place for you to rest.
        But you see, I could only bear fruit when I stood inside your sight.
        Is this what you wanted to see?
        When your tears dry up at last, tell me your answer."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality of despair that has gone through a repeated cycle of faith and betrayal, leaving only the emotion that is expressed through black tears.

        A hero of the past who used to be a guardian of justice. She dedicated her entire life to protect the king, the state, the city, and the weak. The knight had to uphold the laws of God and the pursuit of valor, chivalry, and justice. However, after a long history fraught with hardship and conflict, the knight realized in retrospect that nothing was truly upheld on her watch. The truth changed a lot of people.
        One who fought for good became evil upon realizing that there was no evil left in the world. One who dreamed of a world where everyone could be happy was tinged with greed and started to devour everything. Like them, so many things once thought to be forever constant faced changes and perished

        Who said a knight never cries? Have you ever seen tears brought out by despair, not sadness? The endless stream of grief has long turned the eye sockets into hollow husks. Inside, black diamonds sometimes fall down like ashes.
        The will to protect seems to remain unchanged after all this time; even in containment, it is still obsessed with the act of protection. All that remains is the hollow pride of a weathered knight. The tenacity of the hero who cannot leave the past behind is a pitiful sight.

        When Justice turns its back once more, several dozen blades will rove without a purpose. In shame of failing to defend once again, and in rage against the world, the swords will eventually point at those she could not protect.

        The knight who wanted to redeem herself by saving others was now dishonorably called the Knight of Despair; forgotten from the people's memory, just like the others."</item>
        <item>"If you spot an employee whose face is turning dark green, please report it to the department’s Sephirah immediately. Be advised to verify that the cause of discoloration is not a simple stomachache. When suggested to visit the medical ward, those who have a stomachache would reluctantly agree, but an infected employee would try too hard to act as though nothing is wrong.
        In this situation, try not to alert the employee that anything is out of the ordinary. When the host becomes agitated, the infection will speed up. If the skin begins to change, that means at least 30% of the host's brain has already been consumed. Any conversation at this point is the Abnormality's attempt to mimic the host's behavior, so don't pay it any mind.
        The Abnormality resides inside the host's brain, and the host will not be able to feel any physical sensation. You can try stabbing the employee with something sharp, feigning it as a mistake, but this is not recommended. As mentioned before, the host should already be around 30% merged with the Abnormality, so conversing will be impossible.
        It can enter your body through any aperture.
        This doesn't mean covering up your orifices will impede its entrance.
        But it will help ease your mind to cover up as much as possible when you enter the Containment Unit.
        ‘The Naked Nest's final destination is the frontal lobe.
        You will become the serpent's nest, attacking anything in sight.
        Please understand that we will be forced to fire on sight and burn your corpse should you become a nest."</item>
        <item>"It's not like these kinds of happenings are uncommon here, but one day, dozens of employees were killed in an incident. The reason is the same as always. Something breaches, they attempt to stop it, then it leads to another breach... The one fortunate thing was that the department was sealed off before things could get any worse, so they all died in the same place. Literally, a mountain of bodies was formed. Obviously, no one wanted to clean up that mess.
        Normally, it should have been taken care of within the day, but because the accident was just so horrific and everyone was so exhausted, the clean up was delayed with authorization from the department’s Sephirah. Don't ask me which department it was in, I don't remember all the details.

        When left out in the open, a corpse will begin to rot within a few hours. Most of the bodies that die here are damaged in one way or another, so they decay even faster. You probably don’t know it yet, but most of the employees here are rather skilled at cleaning up dead bodies. Tidying up over and over will make anyone an expert at it, whether you want to or not. Let’s say someone you were just talking to about dinner plans died horrifically. With your repeated experience to help you, you won’t be vomiting or running away at least.

        Whoops, I sidetracked a little there. Anyway, in normal circumstances, the mountain would have been removed quickly, but it remained in the department for quite a long time. So it decayed, melted, corroded, and broke down following the laws of nature.

        That's how its creation began, from the mountains of bodies. The dead gave life to something. Amazed yet? I've still got more to tell you. The dead fused with one another, all smiling. Sharing body parts, at least those that were still intact, they became each other's legs and mouths. That doesn't mean their consciousness has also been restored though. It only wants one thing: our flesh drenched in blood. When there’s an announcement of someone’s death, the first thing you should do is check if this thing’s quarantined. Once it gets a whiff of the scent, it will pursue us in an instant. The smiling faces are unfamiliar yet sorrowful. The more bodies it comes across, the more defined its shape becomes. And it is never satisfied.
        I'm telling you all this because it's almost here. Accidents always happen in this place. Some may spare a bit of their time for a moment of silence, but most will turn away thinking, Again?. At the very least, one thing that was done right is that the department’s been sealed off. I'm the only one left anyways. Did you learn anything from my story? What kind of lesson can be learned from a story as horrible as this, you ask? It's similar to most fairy tales. Don't be lazy is the lesson. When my voice ceases, come here and clean up your colleagues in exactly 3 minutes.

        Pretty soon I won't be able to keep talking. I'm about to swallow a large bomb. Time's running out. Blood is flowing all around here. I'm starting to see the smiling faces now... Something you don't see much of around here. Don't be surprised when you hear a loud explosion. Like I said, it's precisely 3 minutes. I'm sure a bomb this size will be able to suppress it. The last body it finds will be mine."</item>
        <item>"A mechanical Abnormality capable of walking on its own.
        Someone's persistent gaze can be felt from the keyhole inside the machine. It blinks, but never closes. The purpose of the eye or what it is observing is unknown.
        After several experiments, it has been discovered that when one or more employees stare at the Abnormality, the condition becomes far worse.
        Experiment D-002
        An employee was sent in after covering their eyes with a thick cloth. The cloth must be made from a fine opaque material. Tests must be conducted to ensure the cloth completely blocks their vision. After entering the Abnormality's Containment Unit, they faced the direction of the Abnormality for 10 seconds. No reaction.
        Experiment D-003
        Similar to Experiment D-002, an employee was sent in with their eyes covered. The cloth was identical to the one used in D-002, but allowed the employee to discern some forms.
        After entering the Containment Unit of the Abnormality, they faced towards the Abnormality for 10 seconds. After 5 seconds, it aggressively approached the employee. Experiment halted.
        Experiment D-004
        This time, a blind employee* was sent in without any covering. The employee faced the Abnormality for more than 30 seconds. There was no reaction.
        *Please dispose of the subject used in D-004 immediately.
        Memo:
        When training employees who have never worked with this Abnormality before, it goes without saying, but please make sure to tell them not to look at the Abnormality directly. If someone raises doubts about this, tell them what happened to employee Yumi, who didn't follow instructions and stared directly at the Abnormality.
        Memo 2:
        Employee Yumi can no longer be in charge of this Abnormality. She claims that she is under constant surveillance, but this is a preposterous accusation and we believe that she has a severe delusional disorder. Most of what she says is nonsense, but to put it simply, she claims that someone keeps watching her, whether she's eating or going to the restroom. Also, whenever she sees something like a keyhole or a crack between a door, she will become hysterical and try to seal any hole that she sees. However what's more aggravating is that her mental corruption levels read normal, which makes it difficult for us to dispose of her by the system. Please replace her soon…
        Memo 3:
        Oh, the request we made before was resolved. Employee Yumi was found in her room. She covered all the holes in her room with duct tape, including the vent. She even stabbed her eyes out with a pen. The delusional disorder seems to have been resolved as well; she's not muttering nonsense anymore... However, I have to wonder why you would want to send a blind employee to the Containment Unit again. I don't know what Experiment D-004 is about, but I don't think it will do much good..."</item>
        <item>"A heart without an owner; it still beats even after being removed from its body.
        When borrowed, its rate of contraction will double, enhancing the borrower’s vigor and strength.
        Excessive aspiration would bring about unwarranted frenzy.
        Employees who did not attack any targets before returning the heart, or those who returned the heart before 30 seconds had passed entered a state of derangement, repeating mindless killings with their enhanced strength."</item>
        <item>"The old notes are full of incomprehensible cursive letters and writings.
        They once belonged to a researcher who had gone mad during their work. It’s only been partially deciphered, but it seems most of it relates to the various experiments that were conducted in this place.
        It begins with guilt and confessions of unethical experimentation but gradually spirals into madness, overrun with insane and broken up sentences about research toward the end.
        The final chapter ends with the phrase: “Born again.”
        One’s observational skill will improve just by holding this item. However, if it is returned without fulfilling the yearning for knowledge, the incompetent shall explode.
        "</item>
        <item>"A meshing of flesh and scrap metal.
        It is speculated to be a religious artifact, found in the flooded district. In the past, some people sought answers through religion. When an employee offers up a prayer, the flesh begins to move, as if receiving the oration.
        The supplicant will suffer various ordeals in a manner like being put through a trial. Meanwhile, all those around them will recover their ails and woes just as if they were being blessed with redemption.
        And the prayer shall inevitably end with the eternal despair of its worshiper.
        "</item>
        <item>"The sap of a nameless, gigantic tree that roots itself on the edge of the world.
        According to the exploration team, there were a large number of lifeforms around it with a scorched green tint. This was because the sap makes them satiated and contained potent healing agents.
        However, some of our employees who drank the sap melted, leaving smoldering, green remains.
        Other various experiments confirmed that the probability of melting rapidly increases as more sap is consumed.
        Many wondered how such a large tree could prosper all the way out in the barren Outskirts. The lifeforms who consumed its sap became its nutrients sooner or later. The tree simply reaped from what it sowed.
        "</item>
        <item>"It assumes the shape of a cheval glass, but nothing is reflected on its surface.
        The only thing it shows is people. When facing oneself in the mirror, the subject changes. There are numerous suggestions, like the possibility of a linkage to a parallel universe or magical powers, but none of this can be confirmed.
        Those who face themselves in the mirror may appear the same, but in actuality, they have become completely different people.
        Looking into the mirror multiple times will gradually eat away one’s humanity until they become indistinguishable from a hollowed husk of a man, so caution is advised.
        “Yo, Brian just walked right past me without saying a word. What’s up with him?”
        “Oh, he took a peek at the mirror.”
        “Y’know, he always complained about being born too weak. I guess he finally made up his mind about it huh.”
        “The satisfaction is only temporary though.” "</item>
        <item>"A bomb shelter that completely protects its interior from all hazardous influences of the outside world, including light.
        The shelter still retains the memory of that day.
        Company P wished to construct the safest place on Earth. As such, the interior of this shelter houses a large number of non-perishable goods, which would allow anyone who stayed inside to survive for an extremely long period of time.
        Thanks to this shelter, the selected refugees were safely shielded from the ocean of endless screams and bloodshed.
        However, this shelter, while perfectly safe on the inside, alters the reality of the outside to be even more hopeless. It literally makes itself into “the safest place on Earth.” "</item>
        <item>"The Abnormality is similar to a fairy, having two pairs of wings and a small body. They act as a cluster.

        They use a language we cannot understand to communicate with each other. They follow a few employees around when they enter the Containment Unit, using their special abilities to help heal injuries. Employees call this act The Fairies' Care.

        The fairies protect our employees. If you often act out of the goodness of your heart, and are a lover of nature, then the fairies will gladly take care of you. Everything will be peaceful while you are under the fairies' care (you can also enjoy the envious glances you'll get from other employees. Not that it's important, but...).
        What if the fairies don't approach you? Then you should reflect on your life. When Emil and I took shifts entering the fairies' Containment Unit, the fairies did not hesitate to approach me. Only me, never towards Emil. (You all know Emil and how he is. Why, just yesterday he refused to share his snacks with me, and he was acting all high and mighty.)
        It is a sacred act to be protected by fairies in any world. However, do not enter their Containment Unit just to have a bit of fun; if you’ve read a few books on them, you’ll know that fairies dislike those who take advantage of their kindness..

        The corresponding document is only accessible by Employees Level 4 and higher
        When Walter, who was under the care of the fairies, died in the room of another Abnormality, we noticed some anomalies. His stomach and face were ripped off, and his eyeballs and organs were damaged as if they were eaten by something. Moreover, the Containment Unit Walter was found in was for an Abnormality that uses psychological attacks. Meanwhile, the fairies had someone's blood and flesh smeared all over their mouths. We did not bother to examine them to find out whose flesh and blood it was.
        In our world, there are few outcomes that result from perfect kindness. Having fairies that live in a forest visit you just because they like you or that you've done many good deeds is only something that happens in fairy tales. Even though we know this truth, we still sometimes become deluded. Thinking that The Fairies' Care is happening because of all the good deeds we've done, or that the fairies are favoring us because there is something that makes us more special than the other employees.

        The fairies are no more than carnivorous monsters, and their protection is their method to keep the meat fresh. When an employee enters another Containment Unit, they gobble them up in fear that they would lose their food to something else.
        However, the employees were greatly satisfied by the fairies' care, and we saw a drastic decrease in the accident rate, so we deemed it unnecessary to tell the truth to the employees."</item>
        <item>"It's always under the floor of the Containment Unit, only showing its eyes and a mysterious luminous organ above the ground.
        There's no way to confirm what it looks like in its entirety. As it moves underground, not through the hallway, it is impossible to predict its path when breaching. For the same reason, its escape cannot be detected. *

        Lloyd: You're located near the Information Team right? I've heard that some employees went missing around that area. Would you mind checking to see if there's any Abnormalities causing spatial interference?
        Paul: What? But there's no such Abnormality around here. I don't detect any breaching Abnormalities either.
        Lloyd: Look everywhere.
        Paul: Well, Lloyd, there's no sign of any Abnormality, but I do see a small flower on the ground.
        Lloyd: What are you on about? What flower?
        Paul: The bud is glowing, it's amazing. It's strange finding something so green here, when we don't even get sunlight... It's so bright, other employees came over to look at the flower too. You need to come and see it... The light is so bright and warm... I feel like something good is about to happen...
        Lloyd: ...That's not a flower. Order all the employees nearby to evacuate immediately. Do not run away in a group; you have to slowly escape one by one, with quiet steps...
        Paul: What are you talking about, I thought I told you there's nothing nearby... Wait, I think I just felt a slight tremor beneath my feet. Is someone fixing the pipes today?
        Lloyd: Ah, screw it. Just enjoy looking at that flower all you want... "</item>
        <item>"After the popularity of the “All-Around Helper” skyrocketed, “We Can Change Anything” was released as the second installment of XX Inc’s home robot series.
        As to be expected of all of XX Inc’s products, it sports a variety of functions.
        Is your child a troublemaker who cries all the time? We can change that!
        Don’t like how you look? Are you too fat? Too skinny? We can change that!
        Is your house suffering from an outage because you don’t have the money to pay for the power bill? We can change that!
        It’s quite simple. Just open up the machine, step inside, and press the button to make it shut. Now everything will be just fine.
        The machine will produce energy after an employee enters it. Seeing as once inside, nobody ever comes out, it must be rather comfortable."</item>
        <item>"The booking clerk who remains dauntingly quiet sells tickets for a train with no final destination. There are no clocks to alert the arrival times, instead, there are some blinking lights.
        The first and second lights illuminate; your mind clears. The third light illuminates; your mind clears and your wounds close.
        The fourth light illuminates; the condition of every employee in every department improves when you hear the train’s horn off in the distance.
        When the time comes, the train will chug down the tracks and sound its mighty horn. There is no doubt that it will plunge through the endless tunnel while boarding the employees who have not taken a step back from the tracks.
        "</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality taking the form of a straw scarecrow. The straw is stained with blood.
        The head is empty as if someone forcefully tore it off. It shows aggression towards certain employees, attempting to take their brains. These employees are those who scored Excellent on the intelligence test.
        Each city needed to have its own unique technologies; that was the key to reinvigorating the city. There were numerous ones, but among them, one city saw advancements in technology for the replacement of body parts. It was possible to repair or augment body parts that were broken and malfunctioning, or simply undesirable. Every citizen was eligible for that treatment.
        However, rumors circulated. When a rich person looking to improve their eyesight approached a beggar with broken lungs struggling to breathe, they would transplant the beggar's eyes to the rich person. Then they would abandon the beggar's corpse somewhere along the outskirts, still with those rotting lungs.
        The city's representative reassured them, dismissing the rumors as nonsense. To put the rumors to rest, they announced that they would select a number of sick people from the outskirts and fix any body parts they wanted. Out of the lucky few who were chosen, one returned several days later. He had a visibly long scar on his head. People asked him how he felt and he responded that his head felt lighter. He was a man filled with sorrow who used to cry a lot, so everybody believed that the surgery was a success.
        However, when he was asked about the whereabouts of the others who went with him, he just smiled without uttering a word. Before long, even at his parents' funeral, he showed no emotion. All he did after the treatment was stare out the window and talk to himself. Eventually, he hung himself on the doorknob of his house.
        Some people thought that the treatment caused his troubles, but after a few days, he was completely forgotten. The city still remained a beautiful place where the emerald roads sparkled bright as ever."</item>
        <item>"It was a strange phenomenon. It was a phenomenon in and of itself. There was nothing within the unit that could be detected with the naked eye.
        Just like those who had made similar claims some time ago, just because something cannot be seen does not mean it doesn’t exist. The Containment Unit’s square length was XXX meters, and this is the cognitive range of the Abnormality. The only advice that can be given is to remain cautious and aware of your surroundings.
        Breathing will become impossible while within range of the Abnormality. The area will become a vacuum. Strictly speaking, the Abnormality itself is the vacuum phenomenon.
        Record of the Death of Employee Chomsky
        There was no way to confirm if the Abnormality had left its Containment Unit or not. All of a sudden, Chomsky had stopped in the middle of the corridor and just stood there. The hallway was busy at the time with many a person passing by, and of course many of these people expressed their discontent for having part of the hallway blocked.
        Then, all of a sudden, Chomsky’s body suddenly rose over 3 meters into the air. His arms and legs were awkwardly stretched out just as if he were being crucified. If his legs had still been on the ground, he might have looked as if he were performing in an elegant play or doing ballet. Everyone in the hallway stopped to look at him. Then Chomsky started to scream. He screamed like a madman who had witnessed something horrifying. Nobody knew what to do. Some of our employees attempted to pull Chomsky down by the legs. He didn’t budge. After that, Chomsky stopped screaming.
        A short silence followed, and Chomsky opened his mouth, attempting to mutter something. The two employees who were trying to pull Chomsky down started to scream. Blood poured down from his body. His arms and legs separated, leaving his limbless body floating in the air. All hell broke loose in the hallway and everybody began running.
        How to recognize this Abnormality is a matter that needs to be discussed further. Currently, we are researching ultraviolet technology that may be able to detect the Abnormality using the eyes of shrimp, but the performance so far has been far from satisfactory.
        For now, a good method is to have employees entering its Containment Unit bring a glass cup filled only halfway with water. They will need to place this cup on the floor while working. If the cup begins to slosh, threatening to spill over, the employee must stop working and leave the unit immediately."</item>
        <item>"Any attempts to describe (CENSORED) will cause severe mental corruption to both the speaker and the listener. Therefore, it is forbidden to record any depictions of the appearance of this (CENSORED). All audio and written records should be inspected to ensure that such depictions are deleted from them. All work pertaining to this deletion must be designated to Level 5 or higher employees.


        Randy: It's a shame that we have to send such a capable employee like you to its Containment Unit. Do you have any last words before proceeding? Of course, when I say last words, it’s just a precautionary thing.

        (CENSORED): It can't be helped. I'm the employee with the highest resistance against cognitive breakdown. I’ve been apathetic towards everything since I was a kid. People often said I lacked empathy and wasn’t normal. However, when I got to work here, my abnormal ability became the key to save everyone. This is something that can never be experienced anywhere else.

        Randy: Let me say this again. While it is true that you have the highest resistance among employees, that's only based on human standards. If you begin to suffer from a surge of intrusive thoughts, or you decide to count down from ten but fail to remember what ten even is, or feel an uncontrollable regurgitation of vomit or saliva, or if this place starts to feel like somewhere else other than the company, or you suddenly feel insignificant and think that suffocating is your only hope… you need to leave the Containment Unit immediately.

        (CENSORED): If you tell me that one more time, that'll make it thirteen times you've said that now.

        Randy: We cannot monitor you in real time. All cameras are off, and your audio record will only be updated after the work is finished. Needless to say, I'm worried about you. Why don't you repeat the instructions I gave you a bit ago?

        (CENSORED): Go in, don't do the work myself, accompany employee (CENSORED) and observe the work progress. And record everything that happens; even if (CENSORED) is in danger, do not attempt to rescue unless ordered otherwise. Right?

        Randy: Exactly. Now, our contact will be cut off in ten seconds. Good luck and godspeed to your record.

        (CENSORED): I have no regrets. I’d say I’m pretty lucky compared to the others; at the very least I get to leave my last voice record. Well, I say “last” only as a precaution but…

        Randy: All right, your record will be eternally archived and all our fellow employees will remember you. 3... 2... 1... End audio receiving.

        (CENSORED): Randy... That looks, just like our (CENSORED) from long ago, doesn't it? ...Oh, I forgot for a moment that only I can see this. Employee (CENSORED) who was with me became (CENSORED)... It... looks like it can even breed... Employee (CENSORED) who was with me became (CENSORED)... This is just like the process of (CENSORED)... I feel a little sick, but I’m good...
        A small (CENSORED) came out of employee (CENSORED)'s (CENSORED)... I can't believe this... Now it's starting to (CENSORED) employee (CENSORED)... Employee (CENSORED) is screaming like (CENSORED)... The cries... Can you hear them? It reminds me of (CENSORED)...
        Sound: (CENSORED)——————————————————
        Now I see... This is our (CENSORED)... This is the reason (CENSORED) exists... This is the worst thing I’ve seen in my life. I can’t even move. Looks like (CENSORED) has made me its next target. Soon... I will (CENSORED) too... It’s getting closer. I’ll put the recorder in my (CENSORED)...
        I hope this record will help everyone...
        Audio cuts off

        Even after we adopted the cognition filter, many of our managers have lost their minds. Half of them gone because of (CENSORED). Even if we raise the cognition filter to its maximum setting at the risk of having our employees and other Abnormalities being perceived as extremely simple objects, the managers will still be driven insane as soon as this Abnormality comes into sight.
        We can’t make our manager blind just because of one Abnormality. We’re stuck in a dilemma. The only solution we could come up with was at the suggestion of one of our employees. It was to cover the Abnormality with a giant set of censors and blurring. If a flaw in the system disables the censors covering the Abnormality, we will once again have to sincerely consider how to dispose of the manager."</item>
        <item>"An ancient-looking religious book that rests on top of a skinny lectern. Its numerous pages are written on old parchment.
        Its believers prayed that its sanctity would last forever by binding the tome in human skin.
        Those who open the book will be enlightened to unimaginable truths. The ones who have mastered the truths will be called by the prophets; this call cannot be denied.
        Save us now and forevermore. The truth shall set us free."</item>
        <item>"As time passes, people change. We may become disabled, lose our minds, be consumed by overwhelming violence, or be willed to disappear, never seen again.
        This portrait encaptures a moment; it is what we are destined to lose. Those who see their healthy self will subconsciously begin craving. “If life could always be like that. If only I could always have a bright smile just like in that portrait.”
        One will begin to feel strange. One will be unharmed by any shape or form of attacks, however, others will bear the pain instead.
        Little by little, the portrait turned uglier and uglier. Eventually one will stop viewing the portrait and simply enjoy their unexpected luck.
        However, no miracle lasts forever. When all those that bear one’s pain perish, it is their turn to die. Once the person who thought themself to be the luckiest person in the world meets their demise, the portrait turns blank once again.
        "</item>
        <item>"It's a good day! Are you still shy today?
        One sunny day, when they were sincerely drying the laundry in the yard, sadness struck suddenly.
        “In our city, sacrifices for corporates must be highly praised. Honor for their deaths. No reason for you to cry either. Rather, you should be glad.”

        “What's with that look on your face? That kind of facial expression isn't recommended in our city.”

        “Goodness, why are you making such a face? You're making others feel gloomy too. Please be more considerate, you don't live in this world alone after all.”

        “You are very poor at expressing your emotions. You must be quite shy.”

        “Hey, try to look more pleased, that way those living in the Outskirts will be more envious of us.”

        “Put a bigger smile on your face! It's not that hard.”

        “Next time, try to express yourself more clearly, it's very important to express oneself in this society.”

        One sunny day, just like that day they sincerely dried the laundry, they dried their own skin.

        Everyone was finally satisfied when they showed a bright smile. If they met people who asked what was wrong, they would respond: “I'm just shy, that's all. Just shy...”
        If one tries to look at the face behind the skin, the result will not be pretty. The space behind their skin is the only personal space they have left. Leaving it uninvaded is the last bit of generosity the City can offer."</item>
        <item>"An urgent announcement to all personnel in our company. Lobotomy Corporation supports all club activity that promotes positivity. Recently, however, we have received reports that there are group activities plotting unhealthy schemes. Due to constant allegations, we cannot help but take notice of the matter. It is against the company's rules to idolize and/or worship certain Abnormalities. Nothing is allowed to be sacred in this place.
        Employees that try to enter the Containment Units of specific Abnormalities without authorization will face punishment. Especially if they are not in charge of said Abnormalities. If you feel an impulse to throw yourself into a certain Abnormality, that means you are infected. It means that it is in the process of manipulating and dazzling your brain, as do other Abnormalities in this place. If this happens, please stop whatever you are doing and seek immediate mental treatment. As you have all passed basic employee training, we hope no one will be foolish enough to be misled.

        We are releasing the blacklist to the public. Those who are on this list must take 3 days of mental treatment provided by the company and will receive punishment accordingly by their respective Sephirah. We are making this list public to bring your attention to the astonishing number of infected employees around you.
        Please note: Calling Emily—who killed herself after breaking into the Containment Unit of a certain Abnormality—a “martyr” will be treated as noncompliance with the company’s rules.
        On a side note, we would like to praise employee Dylan's courageousness in his rescuing of employee Sophie, who was about to throw herself into a certain Abnormality. If you see any of your valuable colleagues displaying this kind of behavior, please promptly report it to the Sephirah in charge.

        Dylan.
        I don't believe you turned Sophie and us over deliberately. I'm sure you were just worried about Sophie. She's locked up now. I heard that she repeatedly tried to escape, so they tied her to the bed. Tell me, is it wrong to have faith?
        We are all sinners, and our Blue Star is the only sanctuary that accepts us. We will be cleansed of our sins there. We all go back to that place someday. This is an instinct. You thought Emily died when she threw herself into the Star, but she simply returned to her rightful place. She's a martyr. She has become an eternal star. The rise of a star is a brand new beginning.
        Don't you hear the everlasting sound of the trumpet? When you stand close to the Star, you can hear the welcoming cheers and singing. If every employee returns to that place, only Blue Star will remain here.
        Let us meet again as stars."</item>
        <item>"A mysterious worn-out machine used for operations.
        This machine was designed to pull back the skull and destroy nerve tissue safely and efficiently.
        Many of those who underwent an operation inside the machine have found themselves rested and healthy again.
        Those who answered “Yes” to the question “Do you love your city?” were deemed cured. Those who answered “No” weren’t allowed to discharge.
        The longer the machine is in use, the better a person becomes. Furthermore, the longer it is used, the faster the question will change.
        "</item>
        <item>"A bracelet that gives off a soft turquoise light. Many unexplainable things have been discovered in the Outskirts.
        When it is worn, all wounds are healed without a trace of scarring.
        However, to wear this bracelet even when one has not a scratch left on their body is an act of greed.
        This bracelet shall not forgive those who hold greed in their hearts, thus it must only be worn by those in true need.
        "</item>
        <item>"An electronic device with a mysterious symbol engraved into it.
        It readjusts everyone to become righteous, no matter how wicked, evil, and arrogant they may be.
        However, its users will become too dependent on the device and lose all ability to think on their own.
        Eventually, intellect loses all meaning as they forget even how to exist."</item>
        <item>"A mysterious marble which hangs in the Containment Unit.
        We know of an ancient practice; the countless promises that were made, and the unending faith placed in them.
        However, all that they yielded was only hollowness and betrayal.
        Those betrayed hearts sank into the depths, slowly forgotten in the ever-lengthening corridors of time.
        If you make an attempt with an austere heart devoid of desire or expectation, however, you may receive an unexpected reward."</item>
        <item>"Time for the head to burst
        To be frank, life in this place isn't so great. The company says they provide healthy hobbies, but not many people engage in that notion. Everyone looks for their own escape; be it violence, gambling, gluttony...
        I thought I had strength in self-control and discipline compared to others. It did help me live a smoother life. Maybe that's the reason I was assigned to Porccubus' Containment Unit.
        Yes, Porccubus. Where the lowest of the low employees visit. I've heard a bit about what other employees do in that Containment Unit. They call it the game of trust. A game of trust, what an elegant thing to name it.
        (Omitted)
        According to other employees, it wouldn't be too difficult to become intimate with it. And once I get along with it, I could acquire all of it with ease. They said when the time comes, Porccubus will lean down so that I easily reach the thorns. It didn't take long until I got to where I could pet it.
        (Omitted)
        When I first touched its thorns, it felt quite prickly. It felt like a giant needle penetrated my skin. Though there wasn’t any bleeding and the pain went away after a moment. Then there it was, the most intense happiness you'd ever experience. It'd make your knees weak. When I snapped out of it, I found myself drooling.
        It scared me, so I didn't go back for a while. Then, the situation gets worse. You'll get withdrawal symptoms, like retching or sweating. Different employees show different symptoms. One employee even pulled out all their teeth because they felt like bugs were crawling all over them.
        How it felt? I can't find the words to describe it. Remember the greatest happiness you've ever felt in your life? This feeling would be hundreds of times better.
        You say I'm the last employee in charge of Porccubus? That's understandable, as the brain craves more intense stimulation. At first, all I had to do was be lightly pricked by one of the thorns. Now I have to rub my whole body against it to get the same high.
        I feel like all the blood in my body will rush to my head, eventually bursting it. I’ve already imagined my head bursting thousands of times anyhow.
        I have to get going, it's almost time for work. Actually, I’m drenched with sweat right now, did you notice?
        Oh, and Porccubus doesn't show any aggression, unlike your speculation. It didn't eat us or bite our heads off or anything. All the corpses were smiling... happily? That's all. It just makes people smile until death.
        No one is to blame. We have to go through hell every day. We're just having a small taste of heaven.
        You know what? I feel sorry for you. You've never felt these feelings and you never will, but you have to interview an employee on the edge like me while pretending to be decent.
        Now it's time for my head to burst. Good day."</item>
        <item>" 'I wished to sleep eternally.'
        'So don’t bother trying to wake me up again.'
        An Abnormality whose form sports a goat’s fur and horns. It is not unique in regards to its appearance with the exception of several colorful eyes embedded upon its body. Gaining information about this Abnormality is expected to be difficult due to its ceaseless slumber
        The following counseling log illustrates how Void Dream’s ability to make any person slumber psychologically affects the employees. The results indicate that we cannot utilize this ability to reduce the mental corruption of our staff. Please refer to this record for further research.
        Vincent: Please, make it quick... I gotta sleep...
        Counselor: Is that because of the Abnormality?
        Vincent: Yeah, I remember seeing something that looked like a sheep pass by me, and... well, I fell asleep. Since then I’ve been like this.
        Counselor: Do you remember the dream you had back when that occurred?
        Vincent: Oh, I could never forget that dream...
        Counselor: Could you please tell me as much as you can about it?
        Vincent: It was a happy, wonderful, sweet dream. That’s all the words I need to describe it. Heck, I even felt glad to be working for this company. And I saw a guy who’s not with me anymore, he was right next to me... (Omitted) ...Because of that I couldn't get a hold on myself when I woke up.
        Counselor: I see. I’ve heard a little about you from the other employees recently. All of them say that the only thing you do outside of work hours is sleep. Could you please tell me why?
        Vincent: Don’t you understand what I’m talking about? I just want to have that dream again. That dream where I was there with him. Recalling those happy moments... But I couldn’t go back no matter how many times I slept. I slept, and slept, and slept, and slept, and slept, and yet...!
        Counselor: ...I see. I’d advise you to take some rest in your room.
        Vincent: ...They said everyone who woke up after hearing that Abnormality’s sound went mad. People think it’s because they all had a horrible nightmare they couldn’t handle, but it’s actually the other way around. The reality they had to wake up to was so terrible that the soul gave up on waking life. As you know, time flows differently in dreams. A mere instant of waking life constitutes an eternity in the dreamworld. Maybe, if Void Dream were to put me to sleep once again, then I might just have that wonderful dream anew.
        Counselor: ...I’ll prescribe you some sleep medicine. I assure you that it’ll help you sleep. Please get some rest for now. Finally, you will be prohibited from entering the Abnormality’s Containment Unit from now on.
        A demon must change its shape to deceive others. A demon must grant sweet dreams to deceive others. A crack appears in the human mind when it is shown the dream it yearns for. A demon will never miss this chance to bring one to their doom.

        Don’t say such complicated things, don’t say those scary words.
        I just want to grant people sweet dreams; Grant them the enrapturing dreams they want.
        Those who’ve had my dreams are destined to come back to me.
        So, just close your eyes...
        In the dream, your smile was beaming, and we chatted with such liveliness. When I came back to waking life, I realized I was back in a world in which you no longer existed; I felt a void as big as that fleeting happiness I felt in my dream fill my heart.
        I closed my eyes and forced myself to sleep, but morning was still to come no matter what. I think that’s when my soul started to crumble. In fact, I was already broken since the day I parted with you, but I’ve only been acting fine. My soul was already shattering itself into fragments after the passing of that day. Once I saw you again, my yearning for you began to bear down too heavily, I couldn’t ever go back to my old self again.
        Counseling... Rest... All of it was useless. I spent days by myself, agonizing until I finally realized it. It lured me with an unforgettable bait. That was the price for eating away my nightmares. And then it left me with nothing but void, so I would have no choice but to return to it. Then... I have lost to it.
        I don’t want to know anything anymore.
        Please, eat my dreams"</item>
        <item>"A tree that stands in the middle of the Containment Unit. It never withers even if it is not given any form of nutrition. Some employees take time to rest near this tree. Employees sometimes enter its Containment Unit for leisure.

        Pansy: Hey Xavier, did you see that new Abnormality? I think you got put in charge of it.
        Xavier: Yeah, I saw it alright. Just some tree with buds along its branches. I don’t think they’ll be able to blossom without sunlight.
        Pansy: Did you start making observations and writing reports yet?
        Xavier: Nah, I think I’ll get to it soon enough, though.
        Pansy: Alrighty, take care.

        Pansy: Heya, long time no see. How’s it going lately?
        Xavier: Yo, get this! Y’know that Abnormality we talked about before? I don’t think it’s hostile. And guess what? It started blooming! It was so surreal looking at them, it felt like spring had come for the first time in this place.
        Pansy: Is that okay? Usually, any sort of change is a bad omen for something catastrophic here.
        Xavier: Don’t worry, it’s just some harmless little flowers. Thanks for worrying about me though.

        Pansy: Bonjour again. How’s work been going for you?
        Xavier: Golly, the flowers just keep blooming. I think it’ll fill up the whole unit at this rate. You should see it for yourself. It’s really beautiful. I don’t think I’d ever get sick of looking at it.
        Pansy: I’d love to, man, but I can’t. I’ve been so busy lately.
        Xavier: Really? Damn, what a shame... It’s absolutely magnificent, I’m telling ya.
        Pansy: Hmm... You doing alright by the way? You’ve been making a lotta mistakes these days... It seems like you’ve been spacing out a ton too.
        Xavier: Don’t worry, it’s nothing. I gotta head back now. Oh, I’ve been making a sketch of the tree, actually. I’ll let you be the first person to see it when I’m done.

        Audio Recording of Counseling Session
        ...Yeah, I’ve been better recently. I got better at managing Abnormalities, too. Going to Grave of Cherry Blossoms’s chamber makes me feel weirdly amazing, like you said. I never believed that mumbo-jumbo about flora giving out a good aura or whatever...
        But I guess it was true. It’s such a shame I can’t see those cherry blossoms with Xavier. I got to see his work in progress sketch when I was rummaging through his stuff one time. The actual tree was much more beautiful. It was more magnificent than everything he’d described it as. It’s such a tragedy that he went missing before seeing how it is now. If you find any Abnormality suspicious, please make sure you look into ‘em, alright?
        ...Yep, I’m fine now. I shook off that feeling. The cherry blossoms all fell after I saw it that time. Yet, I saw buds poking out of the branches again... Would it be alright if I oversaw the Abnormality from now on? No, it’s no big deal. I just wanna see those flowers in full bloom again. Yes, thank you.

        Notice of Advice
        We’ve received reports about an alarming increase in the number of employees who want to view Grave of Cherry Blossoms’s containment. This fervent rush of requests is likely due to the absence of natural scenery in our facility. However, I don’t think there is any need to make a rule against it. We’ve found that our staff’s mental contamination indices decreased when looking at Grave of Cherry Blossoms.
        The reason behind this is unimportant. It could be “flora giving out a good aura” for all anyone cares. The only thing that’s certain is that Grave of Cherry Blossoms captivates our employees, and they don’t know what lies beneath its roots. Did you realize that the cherry blossoms are strikingly crimson, and its unmatched beauty is caused by its color? The more blood it has, the more beautiful it is. Our employees who are oblivious to it are drawn to it again and again... Just keep everything hush-hush for now. It’s how things work in this place."</item>
        <item>"A long, long time ago in a faraway forest there lived a magnificent bird. Its feathers were wonderfully incandescent, like the tongues of flames, and it was said that they could swallow the blackest of darkness.
        Many hunters longed to obtain even one of its feathers, as it would be their pride and honor. There were many tales about the bird. Some said that those who caught the bird would see their families prosper for many generations. A few even claimed that one wasn’t a true hunter until they had gotten one of the flamelike feathers.
        Others believed that one feather was so strong it could take the owner anywhere they dreamed of. Be what it may, the bird was a symbol of adventure to people. The faraway forest was soon filled with people looking for the bird. Not only hunters, but adventurers and travelers too... The once silent forest became a crowded place.
        People soon became bored with the rumors; they were no longer interested in the hunt. Fewer and fewer people paid any sort of visit to the faraway forest. When the bird finally became nothing but a legend, it experienced a great pain, being blinded. Now all that was left of this legend was a blind bird with bright feathers, alone in an abandoned forest. After a long time had passed, the bird found a new forest. Many people lived in that forest, and the bird just wanted their eagerness to pursue it to once again be stoked like the fiery hues of its blazing feathers. Those who succeed in the hunt are granted with one of the very feathers that countless hunters once yearned for.
        Caution is advised when the hunting season for The Firebird finally arrives. Rash action such as suppressing it is not recommended.
        It is also not recommended to simply hunt the bird to prove one’s bravery. Please remember all the hunters who had to return empty-handed.
        “I can catch it, just a little bit more and I’ll get it…”, every employee has thoughts like this. However, it takes true courage to accept when to give up."</item>
        <item>"The black pendant is darker than any other shade of black, the most obscure of all the forms of darkness in the world.
        Employees should not touch or possess the pendant. Merely looking at it makes one feel as if darkness is creeping into their heart. It seems that this pendant originally made up a circle; however, it is now separated from its other half.
        Many employees called it “The Devil’s Pendant.” Some say just looking at it will fill up your mind with negativity. Employees dislike being anywhere near the thing. After all, it was the polar opposite of its other half.
        Many would let out similar complaints that all ended with the same remark: “We wish it was only the white one.” Its surroundings erode; those who come near it suffer. This wasn’t the result of the pendant’s own volition; those things only happened because of the aura it exudes.
        Then it must wonder:
        “Why do I exist?”
        “If my very existence corrodes my surroundings, and brings suffering and darkness to whoever interacts with me, maybe I shouldn’t have been born at all, just like they say.”
        “Maybe my creator only wanted to make the white pendant, and I’m just an unintentional accident.”
        If so, how can such an impure being disappear from this world?
        One day, the black pendant heard a call:
        “Now the day has come. It is time for us to reunite.”
        The black pendant left the place it thought it would never leave. It found itself swimming away.
        Everything it passed turned to ruin. Destruction was but an instinct. It wasn’t something that could be stopped, nor could it be hidden. It could see the white pendant, no, it could see the part of itself that it hadn’t seen for a long, long time.
        The two opposites were swimming towards each other. For the first time ever, the black pendant felt meaning in its existence.
        “We used to be one. I am, and thus you are. You are, and thus I am.
        We were originally together; it was a fruitless deed to divide us.
        Now you become the sky, and I the land.”.
        An employee who had a face colored with cheerful eyes began to grimace at their sudden burst of sadness. An employee who was quietly crying from having their heart broken dried their tears. An employee who was dragging along their broken leg stood up straight as if they always could. An employee who was on their way to the lounge suddenly fainted, bleeding from every place imaginable.
        As the end circles back to the beginning, those who held hope are met with despair, and those who held despair are met with hope.
        At the end of the beginning, the dragon which now became a great avatar soared through the sky."</item>
        <item>"Half of a pair that is missing each other.
        It reduces the mental damage the wearer has to bear. Because of this, it is called “The Angel’s Pendant.”
        Those who came near it yearned for its energy; they said it cleared their minds, and gave warmth to their hearts. However, they feared the black pendant.
        “I sure wish every Abnormality was helpful like this one.” they would say, sighing.
        Yet, it didn’t understand. It never intended to help others, that was simply what it did.
        However, the world is more than simply warmth and light. The sky exists, for so does the land; darkness exists, for so does light; life exists for so does death; hope exists for so does despair.
        The black carp swims towards harmony. The white carp swims towards chaos. What will happen when the two fish meet?
        "</item>
        <item>"This Abnormality was created with the ideas provided by Tumblbug Backer '정현교 (Jeong Hyeon-kyo).'

        An old clock manufactured by an unknown company. Its vacuum tubes give off a vintage vibe. The manufacturer stopped making these clocks a long time ago.
        “…Is your future totally grim? Have you hit absolute rock bottom, not a single way out in sight? Have you ever thought: ‘Oh man, what if I’d done this instead of that?’
        Humanity has conquered disease and nature. Now we have come far enough to harness time itself.”
        “Yes, we can rewind your wasted time. Just wind it up, close your eyes, and count to ten. When you open them, you will be standing at the exact moment you wished to be in.”
        + Please read the manual thoroughly. You never know what the extremely high voltage discharged from the machinery could do if it is handled poorly.
        We are not responsible for any accidents that may occur from user error and carelessness. This clock requires a high amount of energy to operate. Please understand that it will take a considerable amount of time to charge.
        "</item>
        <item>"This Abnormality was created with the ideas provided by Tumblbug Backer 에레 (Ere).
        An old woman with a piano at her side. Her eyes are usually closed. She only nods instead of speaking, but on rare occasions, she will faintly smile.

        The world’s greatest pianist, *****, always gave her best performances when playing that sonata, her favorite piece. Many praised her excellent skill. Some couldn’t even stay seated when she played the third movement because of the overflowing energy and madness that would come of her performance. In her now empty residence from which she left for the moon, lies the piano she played since childhood, and shrunken heads which allow us to delve into her mind.

        “I mean, we didn’t see anything outstanding when we went to secure it. There was just some lady sitting there. It was like she had been waiting for us to come. What happened when one of us approached her? Well, that guy didn’t know the first thing about art or music, but before we knew it, he was playing the first movement of that sonata. And the lady smiled.
        ...To be honest, I don’t think I’ll ever get to hear a piano performance as beautiful as what I heard then ever again. We never got to see that guy again. That’s why you need my testimony, right?
        Because I played the third movement.
        (Omitted)
        I don’t know how or why it makes you play. Your hands just move, and you feel... euphoric while playing it. Everything around you fades away. It’s just you and the piano. After I finished playing, exhausted, I realized what my feet had been pressing down on weren’t pedals, but severed heads.
        “ ...The moon represents the human psyche.
        They often say that the moon is beautiful.
        But when enough time has passed, when you look at it and see what kind of face it truly wears...
        You’ll realize you were madly in love with something so broken and shattered. In the end, we all become like the moon. All because we can’t bear ourselves.
        "</item>
        <item>"This Abnormality was created with the ideas provided by 'Tumblbug Backer 문정호 (Moon Jeong-ho)'

        This Abnormality takes the form of humanoid creatures in pink equipment. Its intellectual capacity is high enough that it can verbally converse with human beings. At the very least, it seems friendly during observation and work. It has identified itself as a special force from ***** and uses the pronoun “we” when referring to itself. It has continuously shown positive intentions to help humanity.

        Audio Record from First Contact with the Abnormality
        (Omitted)
        Serena: Well, I feel threatened because you’re armed. That bright pink outfit’s disturbing as well. It doesn’t belong in a place like this.
        - What’s your opinion on the nature of humans, Miss Serena?
        Serena: ...I think it depends on a person’s experience. Why do you ask?
        - It is a highly debatable topic, but this is what we think we should do. If a person is good from the start, we protect their good heart. If a person is bad from the start, we will make a good heart out of them and protect that heart.
        Serena: How are you going to do that?
        - We can see the color of humanity’s hearts. The color of the human heart is pink, and by wearing the same color, we can blend in with people’s minds. We will gladly get dirty for the sake of the goodhearted.
        Serena: Wait, you’ll get dirty instead of the people? Is that actually a thing that’s possible?
        - Indeed it is.
        Serena: I’m sorry, but I just can’t trust you or what you say. It’s rather suspicious that you can just “see” the color of someone’s heart.
        - If anything happens, just call us, ma’am.
        (End of recording)

        Following what was stated in the recording, the Abnormality’s will to help others is solid. We have yet to grasp detailed information around this Abnormality. Perhaps actually asking it for help could aid in learning more. However, just like any other Abnormality, we shouldn’t blindly trust it. I plan to have a suppression team ready while I pretend to ask it for help.

        So a lot’s happened up to now. To summarize the whole thing, this Abnormality is the best thing we’ve ever had here. A few months ago, I took a chance asking this Abnormality for help, and ever since I’ve been using it. I’ve gotten help from it about ***** times by now. My efficiency at work has gotten so much better too. At this point, just looking at something pink makes me feel better. Those creatures bolster in a way even the greatest leaders can’t match. This Abnormality will greatly improve our employees’ quality of life.


        Serena: You can do it again today, right?
        - Yes, the human heart is pink, and we wear the same color. We will drive away bad thoughts.
        Serena: You hear that? Yes, it’s still in the best condition. We can put this Abnormality to good use again in our next suppression. They’re so much better than human soldiers. Perhaps we should positively consider putting them as our special suppression team. On a side note, they seem to have gotten a bit darker in color, but I don’t think it’s anything to lose sleep over.
        - The human heart... it’s... we must... clean...
        - Even... the smallest speck... of evil... must... be cleaned...
        Serena: It seems a bit less... energetic than usual. Though it’ll be fine, I think.
        (End of recording)

        Urgent Report of the Incident related to Army in Pink
        We’ve filed this urgent report due to the drastic change in Army in Pink. We’re still trying to grasp exactly what happened. A total of ***** employees have passed away. The following audio is a recording of the assumed first casualty, employee Serena.

        (Audio Recording)
        Serena: An Abnormality has broken out again in the ***** section. I’d like to ask if you could help us out again.
        - Yes... we, the Army in Black... blend into the human heart... and drive away good thoughts...
        Serena: ...Hold on. What? That’s not your line.
        - The human heart... is black... we must... regularly... clean...
        Serena: What are you talking about? You’re creeping me out, man.
        - We’ll protect you with our black love.
        Serena: Stop, I’ll call the suppression team... If you move even an inch I swear...
        - We salute you, ma’am...
        (The recording abruptly ends after the sound of a huge explosion)"</item>
        <item>"A super fluffy ultra-cute puppy with white fur like fresh snow.
        This Abnormality is so cute that just taking a short little glance at it will make you feel so much better. It has the eyes of an angel and is the purest thing in the world. (Further descriptions of this creature have been omitted for brevity’s sake. The rest of the sentences are essentially just saying “It’s so cute!” in various ways.)
        This little Abnormality couldn’t be evil at all. The only thing you have to worry about is your heart aching if you look at it too long because it’s just so cute. In fact, employees who enter this Abnormality’s Containment Unit tend to lose themselves a bit and often need to be forcibly removed from the unit by other employees. Caution needs to be taken as the assisting employees can also become captivated by its cuteness and become lost as well.
        + Attempts to bring the Abnormality out of its unit may occur from time to time, but this is not a concern as they are typically prevented by other employees.
        + When too many employees want to work with this Abnormality, a lottery will be held to decide who gets the privilege of doing so.
        + Our employees tend to show symptoms of mental regression such as oddly toned speech with a high pitch upon entering its Containment Unit, but it seems this is only a temporary problem.
        + Many of our employees refer to this Abnormality as “The Goodest Boy in the World Ppodae”, however, its official designation is simply ‘Ppodae’. Please make sure you don’t get confused.
        ++++ Every employee who enters its Containment Unit must upload a video or photo report of this Abnormality. (This is highly, extremely, UBER important; ensure that nobody misses this step.)
        A company of this size will always have a rumor or two floating around.
        “I heard that you can hear someone’s bones breaking if you walk the hallways at night...”
        “If you try and track down that sound, you’ll find a Yeti who’s eating one of our employees...!”
        “However, we don’t have an Abnormality that looks anything like a Yeti...”

        John: You should be thankful, dude. You’ve got a lucky chance to get to work with The Goodest Boy in the World Ppodae.
        Jacob: Uh... It’s bapping me with its paws. Is this an attack?
        John: He just wants you to feed him. Don’t you know that it’s a trend in our company to always carry a packet of dog food or two?
        Jacob: Well... I don’t really like animals... (John lets out an irritated mumble.) By the way, this lil’ puppy’s pretty beefy. Is that how dogs usually are? I guess this one’s played a lot of catch, huh?
        John: We used to play fetch with him pretty often just to watch how cute he was running after the ball. Though, we stopped for some reason...
        Jacob: Hey, did you see its face when I fed it? It was super creepy, I swear...
        John: It’s just your imagination man. He’s always like our little angel. IsnThatWight? WhosAGoodBoi?
        Jacob: Geez, does this thing have some kinda power to mentally manipulate people?
        John: No idea what you’re on about, Jacob. DoYouDoWiddleBuddie? WiddleCutiepie? DoYouDoYou?
        John: Did you wait for me, Ppodae boy?
        Jacob: Uh, hey, it’s eating something. Aren’t we supposed to be the first people in its unit today?
        John: My widdle goody-good good boi was just hungwy, uh-huh uh-huh. Man, he’s just so cute. Look at how he’s nomming on that~
        Jacob: What the hell is it chewing on... Shit! I knew it! That’s... That’s James’ finger, man! He went missing during the last patrol shift! Can’t you see the nail?! Remember him bragging about having a heart painted on his nails? I told you, dude! This thing’s up to no good!
        John: I... I can’t believe it... who...
        Jacob: This Abnormality’s the killer! I get that you’re shocked, but I told you a bunch of times that there’s no way a “cute” pet could be harmless in this place. Man, I’m glad you finally came to your sen—
        John: Who... Who wouldn’t feed him on time?!
        Jacob: ........
        John: Poor little guy’s been starving all night! It’s... It’s so heartbreaking...
        Jacob: Well uh... I think we’re supposed to suppress it?
        John: How could you even suggest doing something so heartless to a cute little good boy like this? Just wook at his eyes... How could an innocent animal do anything wrong? IsnThatWightYouGoodWiddleCutieBoi.
        (The Abnormality shows no reaction. Only the sound of a bone being gnawed on is audible.)
        Jacob: Dude... your “little angel” is gnawing on our colleague’s finger.
        John: What are you, a newbie? Don’t you know everything cute is forgiven here?
        Jacob: I’ve never heard that, and I seriously don’t think it’s true. We’ve gotta tranquilize it. And if you won’t, then I’ll do it by myself!
        (The sound of a tranquilizer shot being fired can be heard.)
        John: NOOOO!!!!!
        (The Abnormality begins to whimper.)
        (The recording cuts off after a bit of shouting.)
        ...Following the evidence I’ve provided in the recording, I request that Jacob be immediately demoted for firing such a thing at Ppodae. A terrible, evil animal abuser has no place working in our company. Our Goodest Boy in the World Ppodae has been traumatized. Traumatized!
        By this incident. He’ll only eat 5kg of his favorite snack now. To help him cope with the trauma, I suggest we request a new snack for Ppodae: “Premium grade salmon rich with Vitamin B”. I’ll be waiting for your reply.
        Reply:
        Your requests have been accepted.
        P.S. In your next message, please make sure you attach 5 different photos of The Goodest Boy in the World Ppodae. Thank you in advance."</item>
        <item>"An Abnormality taking the form of a tree with plentiful leaves. The leaves are lush with a rich green color, creating a comforting ambience. A refreshing flowery scent is carried by a gentle breeze.
        Employees who made contact with the Abnormality stated that it provided them a significant psychological comfort. Such statements were deemed truthful as the employees displayed a visible increase in work efficiency, along with a notable decrease in mental corruption.
        An Excerpt From an Employee’s Diary
        At first, I thought it was just my imagination from being sleep deprived. But as my body and mind got more and more exhausted, the voice calling me got clearer and clearer.
        ‘I can help you with your problem.’
        Yeah, that’s right. You can help me. What was I worrying about?
        I can smell a flowery scent….
        They imported a tree. That tree, standing in the middle of the Containment Unit, was such a beautiful sight to behold. I could feel the scent of flowers flit across my face even though there was no breeze or wind. Smelling that scent for even just a moment makes my attachment for the tree blindly grow. I was very intuitive since my childhood, so I could sense that this artificial attachment was hazardous.
        Ever since then, I tried everything I could to avoid contact with that tree, making all kinds of excuses whenever I was assigned to work on it.
        “Well, if you put it that way… just this once, okay? Geez, did that tree do something to you?”
        My colleague’s banter gets stuck in my ears. Did it do something? Yes, it did, and it scares me. A few days later, the same colleague has now become a staunch worker, wearing a constant smile on his face. I knew he’s always been an optimistic person, but I couldn’t help but feel uneasy because his face seemed strangely comfortable.
        “Really, do I seem content lately? Yeah, well, that’s because the tree is helping me out.”
        He answered light-heartedly. From my years of experience, I can say for certain that few people can smile so sincerely while working for this company. That means, when someone keeps smiling at work, it’s a sign that something went wrong. My suspicion immediately led me to report this behavior to my superior.
        The answer came sooner than I thought. It said that I am to observe the Abnormality myself and file an observation report because there have been several abnormal behaviors related to this tree which were identified in several other employees, not just the guy I reported.
        The order forced me to finally confront this tree that I had been avoiding as best I could. I knew I couldn’t pass it over to someone else this time. It was no longer a barren, naked tree that I saw the day it was imported. Instead, I saw a Containment Unit covered in grass that seemed to be sprawling around the tree. Which was peculiar, since there’s no way grass can grow in a Containment Unit. This facility is completely inorganic.
        ‘Hello, have you come here to receive my blessing, too?’
        The moment I felt that something was wrong, a voice echoed in my head….
        (It was difficult to decrypt the contents of the diary from this point onward as the writing becomes heavily distorted)
        I don’t know how I wrote the observation report, all that’s certain is I just wrote what I felt about the tree: This beautiful plant is bringing happiness to every employee who visits its Containment Unit; it will soon greatly contribute to humanity’s quest for prosperity and advancement.
        But how could an Abnormality be such a good influence on humanity?
        ‘I just want to help you.’
        A voice without a single speck of malicious intent echoed again in my head. Yes, you’re right. You’re just helping me.
        ‘And if you’re okay with it, could you bring all your friends who are having a hard time here? I believe I can help them.’
        Yes, this tree will easily bring peace to their mind. Speaking of which, that newbie seemed to be pretty depressed lately.
        “Hey, I know a place that’ll make you feel better. Come along if you want to.”
        She followed me without any suspicion. It wasn’t hard to bring her to the tree’s Containment Unit. I offered her to the tree. She could get better; she will get better.
        ‘You’ve brought your friend. You are a good child. Let me gift you with something.’
        I could feel something sprouting from my body. I couldn’t move my limbs. No, this isn’t a bad thing, I am being reborn with the tree...
        The tree has entered me, transfixed me. We proliferate and become whole. Ah, I can completely feel it now.
        "</item>
        <item>"This Abnormality was created with the ideas provided by Tumblbug Backer 'mul'.
        A melting slime with a resemblance to humans when inspected closely. Its Containment Unit is covered in its mucus secretions.
        Today, I’d like to talk about the recent incident everyone has heard of. That’s right, that dreadful incident when an army of slimes took over our facility for ***** minutes. There were several containers left in the ***** lab which were not processed properly during the experiment related to *****.
        If you know about the ***** experiment, you would already know that the contents of those containers are merely useless leftovers that only prove the experiment has failed. Our researchers felt there was no need to dispose of them.
        It was obvious that one newbie to the research team had no idea what was inside those containers. Employee Marie found the containers of pink slime and felt that they could pose a threat. It is assumed that she thoroughly concealed and kept them in ***** status. If my assumption is correct, the melted object in those containers was probably the ***** of *****. I became sure of this when I read the passage that described its appearance as that of an adolescent human.
        I dunno if it was fortunate for us or not, but its memories, including those of the experiments, were completely gone; it could barely speak a word or two. It was also mentally unstable. It became extremely nervous whenever Marie was not present.
        A brother. Marie had a brother whom she lost during her childhood. It all started when she felt an attachment to the childlike pink slime that followed her around. Marie showed an unprecedented level of decrease in her mental corruption. Indeed, it was extremely unusual. Of course, it was certain that the Abnormality somehow affected her in a positive way, but that was the end of the benefits.
        Her colleagues started noticing her odd behaviors; they tried to ask her about them, it was the right thing to do. They were educated about the potential implications of a steep decrease in mental corruption levels, and understood that a person disappearing every single break time is a dangerous sign. However, Marie didn’t say a word to them and ended up detained in the counseling room until she opened up.
        Meanwhile, this slimy creature that had forgotten everything instinctively remembered one thing: it had to get out of the facility no matter what. This Abnormality once again felt extremely nervous when Marie didn’t show up on time. It thought that she was in danger; it was then that it decided to escape WITH her. A rare bond had formed between the two. They cared about each other from the bottoms of their hearts.
        Confined within the counseling room, Marie eventually gave up her right to remain silent and began to reveal what she had done. How she kept the contents inside the container, and how she was able to form a bond with it. However, she couldn’t finish her words. This was because she melted in the blink of an eye, moments after signs of an anomaly showed up on her skin. Yes, she quite literally melted, melted in her entirety. And that wasn’t the end of it. The slime that once was Marie a few seconds ago began to move. It wasn’t a difficult task for a fluid creature to slide under the door of the counseling room.
        Did it have a speck of human rationality? No. Just like a newborn duckling blindly follows its mother, it simply moved towards the Abnormality. And it wasn’t just Marie that turned to slime. Every single employee who had made contact with her in some way began to melt too. Those who were questioning her, who had shared a meal with her, who had worked together… Soon, this army of slime began to attack other employees. All for the mother slime, the Abnormality they loved. Yes, out of love and love alone, they killed.
        ...and my dear employees, I do hope you all didn’t forget to put on the gas masks we distributed to you before we entered, did you? I do hope that no one took it off out of boredom or stuffiness. I must inform you all that some of you are already infected by the slime I told you about. We did not give gas masks to some of you, and we did say that it was because we were out of stock. Though, to be truthful, it was just so we could distinguish between those who are infected and those who are not. You may feel fine now, but before an hour passes, your flesh and bones will start to melt, and your mind will disintegrate into pitch-black nothingness. Then you will begin trying to wreak havoc on the facility. You’ll probably, as your first action in your new form, jump at the employees sitting right next to you. All for the mess of slime you so adore.
        Yes, I know. It’s unbelievable. You feel so alive and clear now, just how on Earth could you melt down into slime? And yet you will. It’s not your fault of course. Someone among you made contact with the slime Abnormality, and you were just the unlucky sap who happened to be around that person. It’s meaningless now to determine patient zero. I doubt they had any idea how catastrophic the results of their actions would be. They did it out of pure affection, after all.
        Finally, those uninfected who are wearing masks, please ensure you pay extra attention to your hygiene and immediately report when you see an employee acting out of the ordinary. You’ll simply be infected as well if you attempt to help them. Now, in your desks, there will be 9mm pistols, all perfectly locked and loaded. What you must do now should be clear. We will not open the doors until the situation is… taken care of. If you think this too cruel, allow me to remind you that this is your job. I hope to see you again once everything has been handled."</item>
        <item>"In the ***** century, a monk named ***** from the province of ***** walked a path of Buddhism, seeking liberation and true enlightenment. He was on the road to his home country to spread his philosophy, when he heard that an old monk was being cremated in the nearby town. He felt that he should go witness it, however, a man stopped him.
        Excuse me, sir. There's a rumor that an evil spirit lingers in the town you’re heading towards. The monk replied, Evil spirits are naturally born from one’s heart. How could I miss the cremation of a great monk simply because a rumor has been spread? He then continued on his way to the town of *****.
        When the monk arrived, people from all around the town were gathered in ceremony. They were gazing at the corpse of the old monk, chanting the name of Guanshiyin.
        Guanyin!
        Guanyin!
        Guanyin!
        The chant was born more out of desperation for something they yearned for, rather than commemoration. The funeral pyre started crackling as it was fed with kindling. The sound of wooden percussion echoed, and the chanting grew louder and louder. Soon, the crowd started buzzing with nervousness.
        ...Something’s not right.
        People were massively disappointed by the amount of sarira.
        The people were greatly disappointed by the amount of sarira that appeared. There were no more than two spoonfuls. Shocked, the people soon turned into an angry crowd.
        It makes no sense that such a great monk had such little sarira!Clearly he was lacking in his practice of asceticism!”He must not have done many good deeds.
        The visiting monk was himself baffled. He was unfamiliar with such an obsession with sarira at a cremation, and even he was expecting the proper amount of sarira that a great monk would deserve.
        The monk spoke to a man behind him in the crowd.
        How can they be so upset at such a sacred ceremony?
        A slight distance away, a very old man in the crowd answered instead.
        The poor and hungry yearn for miracles to save them. By how you’re dressed, I would guess that you are also on the path of a Buddhist. This event must have worried you.
        The monk responded in a slightly disturbed tone.
        Sarira forms when a monk has bettered his body and spirit, and finally reaches nirvana. It is a natural process and not to be artificially wanted. How can you call it a miracle?
        The old man then burst out in laughter.
        This monk was known well here for his good deeds. He shared his food with the hungry, and clothes with those who were cold. However, as they say, it seems he was unable to reach true nirvana, as only two spoonfuls of sarira were found. He ended up being a miserable old monk who couldn’t achieve nirvana even though he was a well respected man, and known as a benevolent living saint. Do you think you will be any different?
        I… I have proudly practiced—
        They say a monk from the temple of ***** had earned more than three hundred spoons of sarira. Colorful lights sparkled across the sky as the crowd paid devout prayers at his cremation, and his sarira were as round as pearls. The emperor himself ordered for four temples to be built in his name.
        The monk could not reply.
        ...But, the creation of sarira is a natural process all go through—
        It is well known that Buddha’s sarira were enough to fill a grand palace when he was cremated. One day, your body shall fail and eventually lead you to the eternal heaven. Someday, people will be there for your cremation, just like now.
        The monk was silent.
        If nothing is found in your ashes, you will be a sinner of the trailokya, and your path will ultimately reach nowhere. However, if enough sarira are found from you that everyone looks on in awe, your name will be sung for generations. The emperor will be awestruck and build a huge temple in your name, and the people will chant while admiring the pagoda of that temple.
        ...
        This feeble old man is telling you all this because I can see you becoming one of the greatest monks. Listen, a few hours' walk from here, there is a mound we call *****. Go up there, and you will see several old pagodas. Inside of them are the boxes of sarira from long-forgotten great monks. Why, they’ll just return to the soil if nothing happens to them. But if you were to consume them, perhaps, you would display more sarira than Buddha himself…
        The monk then realized that the old man was suspicious, and did not sound as an old man should. However, the old man was gone in a flash as he tried to catch a glimpse of his face. The monk concluded that it must have been a trick of the devil, and tried to forget what the old man had said. But the old man’s voice lingered in his ears even as he tried to sleep.
        The monk tossed and turned and couldn’t fall asleep. He decided the best way to clear his mind was to go on a walk. As he walked, he somehow found himself around the pagodas the old man had mentioned. They were supposed to be a few hours' travel from where he had been staying. For a long while, only a chant of Om ami dewa hrih echoed around the pagodas.

        They say at night a mysterious sound can be heard around the pagodas and statues in the area of *****. It is said that the source of this sound is a preta: a demonic creature with long arms, claws, and an unnaturally big mouth. Some say this creature carries a shattered japamala, however the exact details are unconfirmed.
        After this creature appears, people find that offered sarira boxes are forcefully opened with their contents removed. Furthermore, monks who stay in this province must not sleep alone. They should also visit a nearby temple to receive a talisman that wards off evil spirits and ensure that they carry it at all times.
        This tale has become widespread across the region, and has led to the tradition of chanting certain lines at pagodas where sarira is stored when cremation takes place:
        亦僧子乎 (Yì sēng zi hū)
        亦僧子乎 (Yì sēng zi hū)
        今汝不必僧 (Jīn rǔ bùbì sēng)
        魔羅汝不極樂往生 (Móluó rǔ bù jílè wǎngshēng)
        The chant translates into this:
        Are you a monk?
        Are you a monk?
        You are no longer a monk.
        A demon shall never reach heaven.
        This chant is orated to the monk who has not yet realized that he has become a demon."</item>
    </array>
    <array name = "good_result_anom">
        <item>"4-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"12-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"11-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"14-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"27-33 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"19-30 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"14-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"14-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"14-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"9-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"26-35 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"12-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"9-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"18-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"13-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"12-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"21-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"14-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"21-30 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"15-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"10-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"28-33 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"15-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"18-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"13-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"23-30 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"25-32 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-22 E-Boxes"</item>
    </array>
    <array name = "normal_result_anom">
        <item>"2-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"5-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-11 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-13 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-26 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"13-18 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-13 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-13 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-13 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"5-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"16-25 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"6-11 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"5-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"5-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"5-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"10-17 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-11 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"13-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-13 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-20 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"6-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"3-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"9-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"17-32 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"7-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-27 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"9-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"4-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"11-17 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"9-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"7-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"13-22 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"8-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"15-24 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"7-14 E-Boxes"</item>
    </array>
    <array name = "bad_result_anom">
        <item>"0-1 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-4 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-4 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-15 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-4 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-4 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-4 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-9 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-5 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-2 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-16 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-3 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-10 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-8 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"n/d"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-12 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-7 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-14 E-Boxes"</item>
        <item>"0-6 E-Boxes"</item>
    </array>
</resources>